Space. What is it?
The simple answer is we don't know
Or at least we didn't know until now.
Hello, I'm Douglas Reynholm
and I'm not a scientist,
but I do have a better understanding
of what space is
than any scientist living today.
Where did I gain these insights?
From this man.
The founder of Spaceology,
Beth Gaga Shaggy,
no relation to either Lady Gaga
or Shaggy,
is the founder of Spaceology,
a religion, not a cult.
In other words, when it comes to space,
he's the man with his head
screwed on tight.
This is what he told me
when I met him on holiday two weeks ago.
Space is invisible mind dust
and stars are but wishes.
I mean, think about that!
That means every star
you can see in the night sky
is a wish that has come true.
And they've come true because of
something he calls Spacestar Ordering.
Spacestar Ordering is based
on the twin scientific principles
of star maths and wishy thinking.
If you'd like to know more,
there are thousands of
Spaceology centres all over the UK.
If that doesn't convince you,
well, then, maybe you just don't deserve
to get what you want.
Ding!
Wow. You're a genius, Ray!
Love the special effects!
How did you do that thing
where I'm spinning around?
Well, in that... In that bit,
you're actually spinning around.
Well, I'm glad you like
the website, Mr Reynholm,
I did spend quite a lot of time on it.
It's brilliant, and well worth
every penny of the £50.
Hundred... Didn't we say £100?
I never would have agreed to that.
Ah, Jen!
Guess who wanted a helicopter
this time last week
and now, thanks to Spacestar Ordering,
has one?
You?
I'll give you a clue,
it ain't these chaps!
You?
You're a sceptic, Jen.
You should be more like these.
They can't get enough
of my Spacestar Ordering story.
Yes, yes, I noticed
you've been coming down here
a lot more often
because of all the questions.
So, Mr Reynholm, how did the cosmos
grant you a helicopter?
Well, I visualised the thing I wanted.
In my case, it was a helicopter.
I drew a picture of the helicopter
on a piece of paper,
then I stood with my back to space,
threw the paper over my shoulder
and wished really hard.
But when you say that you stood
with your back to space...
- Yes.
- How exactly did you achieve that?
I waited till night-time.
Of course.
Couple of days later,
bought myself a helicopter.
Explain that one, if you can.
I wish the cosmos would make it
slightly harder to find our office.
Don't worry, Jen, you'll get your wish,
just as one day I'll get my robot hand.
Scientific mind,
believes in Spacestar Ordering.
Who's getting the robot hand first?
Hey, you're still up for tonight, right?
I'll go if Moss goes.
Sorry, Jen.
I find music confusing and annoying.
Roy invited me to a gig once.
I didn't really enjoy it.
You went to the wrong address!
You went to a swimming pool.
Are you sure it's not swimming pools
that you find confusing and annoying?
You're right.
It's not music I hate, it's swimming!
You know what? I will come, Roy.
Where's Moss? I can't believe
he's missing out on this!
Where are they?
I'm going to have to go and dance
up the front.
- Aren't you a bit old for the front?
- I'm 31 .
Good for you, mate!
Careful! My foot!
Will you chill? Will you chill out, man?
Ow! Jesus Chr...
Get out of town!
You hooked up with someone
from the band?
- Yeah.
- Wow, who was it?
- Norman.
- Norman? Oh, he's the drummer, right?
The keyboard player.
The keyboard player?
Okay.
- What?
- No, it's just...
The keyboard player? Really?
- Yeah, what?
- Well, it's just...
He's a bit geeky, isn't he, Jen?
I didn't think that was your type.
Jen's going out with a geek!
Are you sure it's not just
because he's in a band?
Yes. I really am that shallow, Roy.
- I know you are.
- Yeah, I'm that shallow.
You are, though.
I mean, you really, really are!
Look, I... I like him.
He doesn't say a lot,
he's more of a thinker.
I think he's really cool.
It's because he's in a band!
Oh, flippin' hell.
- Is this your back again?
- When did mosh pits become so unruly?
I told you, you should get a massage.
Oh, I've never enjoyed having massages.
I don't like being naked
in front of strangers.
And I can never relax if I think
someone might play Norah Jones.
Who wants to hear another
Spacestar Ordering success story?
Oh, wait, wait! Yeah, yeah. Okay. Okay.
Go!
Right. Last week, I decided I wanted
to learn how to do tattoos.
So, I did the business,
bought a book on tattoos, read it
and now I know how to do tattoos. Look!
- My helicopter!
-  Oh!
- Oh, that's brilliant.
- Let me see... Oh!
What the bloody hell's wrong with you?
Oh, no, I have a really bad back.
You should see a masseuse.
Don't see a masseuse!
They're the biggest con
of the 20th century.
I had a bad back and I cured it,
thanks to the techniques outlined
in this groundbreaking exposé
of the massage industry.
Go like this.
And push your back up.
Oh, for... Oh!
- That's worse! That's way worse.
- It's terrible, isn't it?
You told me that would make it better!
No, no, no!
That's how I originally injured my back.
- You all right?
- Yeah, feels so much better already.
So that's why I ended up
joining the parachute regiment.
Ah, yeah, the Paras...
That's the one I would have joined.
But you know, fear of heights.
- Were you in the army?
- No.
Oh!
Right, I'll do a little bit of work
on your thighs.
Oh, yeah, hey,
you do what you need to do.
Did you see that ludicrous display
last night?
What was Mancini thinking, eh?
The thing about Arsenal is,
they always try to walk it in.
Arsenal?
Whoever we're talking about.
Ah! Nearly done.
Oh...
Oh, thanks again, man,
this really does feel so much better.
- Right.
- Oh, yeah.
There we are. All finished!
Mwah!
# I love him,
I love him, I love him so... #
Goodness me!
What... What... What would you term
what just happened there?
Norman says my voice is extraordinary.
He's right.
Oh, this is it, you know.
This is the guy. This is the big one.
There's nothing about him I don't like.
When he's asleep, he makes this sound,
a lovely little gentle purr.
-- Oh, that...
Oh!
This is a long song.
Do you know, the last few days
have been indescribable.
Good.
Oh. Hi, Roy!
Hi, Roy.
What?
You okay?
Are you all right?
Is your back still hurting?
Didn't you go to see the masseuse?
Yes, I did.
Did it help?
No.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
It's just that you've got the same face
that you have when you eat vegetables.
Okay.
Something happened.
Something happened?
Yes. When I was getting the massage,
the masseuse did something.
Go on.
Okay, I'm going to tell you,
but you have to promise
not to laugh at me,
because this whole thing
has left me very shaken.
Okay. I promise I will not laugh.
Okay.
He kissed me on the arse.
Sorry, I may have
misheard you there, Roy.
What did you just say?
I was enjoying the massage,
everything had gone very, very well,
but then, at the end,
he just leaned down
and he gave me a big kiss on the arse.
And you thought I'd find that funny?
Well, yeah, I suppose I did.
On what planet would that be funny?
Whereabouts on the arse did he kiss you?
I don't know, just to the left of the...
The line that goes down the middle.
- The cleftal horizon.
- Is that what it's called?
Yes, it is, but never mind that.
What happened next?
Well, then I just got dressed
and I left.
Okay. Okay.
Have you told Jen this?
No, I was really afraid
she'd laugh at me.
Do you think Jen's a monster?
She wouldn't laugh!
This man crossed the line.
He is a member of
the medical profession.
Roy, look at me.
Look at me.
There is nothing funny about this.
I think he crossed the line.
I don't think it's funny.
I mean, I was so relaxed and then
that just tensed me right up again.
My hands were like that for an hour.
I couldn't get them into my pockets
to pay him.
You paid him?
Roy, I've got to tell you,
I think you've got grounds to sue.
Really?
What is that?
That's Jen. That's what she does now.
You should tell her.
- What?
- Listen to this.
Jen, you know that I went
for that massage?
- Yeah.
- You are not going to believe this.
The bloke who did it
kissed me on my arse.
Whoa.
No, Jen, my masseuse
kissed me on my bum!
My body went into spasms!
My hands were like this for an hour!
Stop it! You're killing me!
You've got to spread
that kind of material out!
I can't believe this!
So what's the problem?
I know! He doesn't write,
he doesn't call...
What, did you think
he was coming on to you?
I don't know!
Oh, maybe he's like the Michelangelo
of physical therapists
and that is his signature.
Maybe he does it to everybody.
Look, to be honest,
I don't care why he did it.
All I know is that I was vulnerable.
I was naked
and he kissed me on my bottom.
And I'll tell you something.
This is not the last
that he has heard of me.
As God is my witness,
no man shall ever have to be kissed
on his bottom unexpectedly
because of this man ever again!
Will you stop laughing?
This is the first time
I've left before you.
We're looking up legal precedents
of Roy being kissed on the arse.
Don't sue him, Roy.
You'll get on the news.
- Don't listen to her.
- Everyone will laugh!
No one will laugh! Come on, Jen.
Help us bring this monster to justice!
I can't.
The band are playing a new song tonight,
they want my opinion.
You know to just say it's great, right?
Roy, I am a person,
with thoughts and opinions.
No. You're not.
Jen, please, just say it's great.
When people like that ask you
what you think,
all they actually want to hear
is that they're geniuses.
Goodbye.
She is evil.
Spacestar Ordering success story
number three.
My tattoo got infected,
so they've had to cut off my arm!
I am getting a robot hand!
# In the water
# I am beautiful #
Beautiful. Really beautiful.
Thank you.
It's just a great song.
Really, really great.
If you put a gun to my head
and forced me to give one criticism,
it'd be that maybe it goes on
just a bit too long.
Apart from that, perfect.
Okay.
Listen, Tim, Mary's not
going to make it tonight.
What are we going
to do about backing vocals?
Oh! Oh, I'd love to!
Moss, can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Do I have to testify?
I can't make that decision for you, Roy.
You've just got to ask yourself
one thing.
If you don't take the stand,
how many more unsolicited bum kisses
will be administered
by that lip-happy bastard?
No, you're right, I know you're right.
I do want to testify.
I'm just afraid that
they're all going to laugh at me.
What if they're all...
What if they're all like Jen?
They're not going to laugh, Roy.
No one's like Jen. No one.
I've come to realise she's actually
a very odd person.
Wow. Well, good luck tonight, everyone!
Are you a big Stevie Nicks fan, Jen?
Stevie Nicks? Yeah, yeah. Oh, God.
Thanks so much for this, guys.
I'm so excited.
I've never done anything
like this before.
I can't believe you want me to do it!
I won't let you down.
So, Norman, we've had a talk.
And we think we're going to go back
to not having a keyboard in the band.
Oh, no!
Yeah, I'm sorry but...
We'll see you both again soon, yeah?
Wait! I'm out, too?
And the defendant gave no indication
that he had any intention
of kissing you on the bottom?
No indication whatsoever.
He just kissed me on my bottom.
Out of nowhere.
What was the result?
Well, I had nightmares about it.
And I can't stop washing my bottom.
And I find it hard to trust masseurs.
Where exactly did he kiss you?
- It was in the middle.
- In the middle of your bottom?
Well, just to the left
of the cleftal horizon.
In layman's terms, please, Mr Trenneman.
Oh, I'm sorry, Your Honour.
Just to the left of the bum line.
Just above the thigh?
Well above the thigh.
It was on my bottom.
Although it is true, is it not,
that what some people
might call their bottom,
others might call their hip?
No, he kissed my bottom, sir.
- But is it not true...
- He kissed me on my bottom!
Why... Why... Why is no one laughing?
It's no laughing matter, Jen.
We Spaceologists take
this kind of thing very seriously.
Oh. Are all these people Spaceologists?
Yes, this trial could bring
the massage industry to its knees.
And you'll find they take this case
with the gravity it deserves.
Perhaps Mr Trenneman might be able
to help us with the aid of this diagram.
Could you please place
this picture of the defendant
on the area where you say he kissed you?
That was where the incident happened.
I think that's accurate.
- Oh, you think that is accurate?
- Yes.
Oh, because only a moment ago
you were quite sure,
yet now you only think.
You're twisting my words.
Is it not true that this
may simply be an artist
proud of his work,
signing off with a flourish?
That is not the point.
Yes, thank you, Mr Trenneman.
That will be all.
My arse is not a canvas!
I said, that will be all, thank you.
My bottom is not a kissing post, sir.
Okay, you can dress this up
however you like
with your fancy words,
but the truth remains
that that man sitting there
kissed me on my bike rack
and I was not expecting it,
and it rendered
an expensive massage worthless.
Your Honour, please...
And I am here today
so that no man need be kissed
on his sweetmeats
by this man ever again,
unless they have arranged it beforehand
for some reason.
Will you be silent?
I will not be silent!
I will never be silent!
I will not stop until those lips
are behind bars.
How dare you? I trusted you.
My trouser hams are not for sale, sir!
I put my arse in your hands.
I rest my case.
I'd have used my robot hand for good.
Wake up!