- Who owns the Infinity Gauntlet?
- Thanos.
- What was Thor's father's name?
- Odin.
Sorry, Moss,
I've really got to go.
Just a few more,
just a few more!
No, no, I'm sorry.
You've done more than enough.
OK. Alright, baby,
see you later. Bye-bye.
- Wow!
- Right?
That's an impressive knowledge
of the Marvel universe.
- I know.
- Well, you've done it.
You've finally found a woman
I can do business with.
Yeah, no, don't say
things like that.
I'm sorry, I'm just
so excited for us!
No.
If you don't go in all the way,
it doesn't really count.
Hey, Red! Stand back,
stand back, this one's mine.
I'm going to do everything
for you really nice.
Stand back, stand back!
she's all mine.
- It's tight.
- You're so strong.
- Oh!
- Ah, yes, yes!
It's bubbling over.
It's on the house...for you.
- Oh, my God!
- You inspire me.
- Have a great day.
- I will. And you. Thank you.
Ciao.
Maman, je suis un bébé.
Moss, have you seen this video
of the baby speaking French?
It went viral at 10:30, Roy.
Of course I've seen it.
I must have been in the toilet.
Ah, Jen, exciting news.
I've just uploaded
the second episode
of my board games
review show.
Care to have a look?
That was fast.
Seems like only yesterday
we had to sit through
the last one.
- It was three months ago, Jen.
- Really?!
It feels like it just happened.
Roy, did you hear that?
Moss has done his board game
review show again.
I'm not watching that.
I'm not watching that again.
Jesus Christ, we don't
have to watch it, do we?
We only sat through the
first one the other day.
- It was three months ago.
- My God!
Wow. It feels like
it just ended.
It was so boring!
It was like being insane,
it was so insanely boring.
Roy's not a fan,
but you said you liked it.
- Where did you get your coffee?
- New place.
- Any good?
- Really good.
You specifically said,
and I quote,
"You must show me
the next one, Moss."
- Did I? Did I really? My God.
Oh, if you'll excuse me,
that'll be my lady love
from the seventh floor.
- That's going well?
- Oh, yeah!
He's cock-a-hoop
over this sheila.
OK, so that'll be over soon,
then.
Hey, I'll have you know that
Alice is nuts about me.
She thinks that
I'm emotionally artistic.
What does that mean?
Well, she said that emotionally
I was on the artistic spectrum.
I think it means that I'm
creative about my feelings,
and I'm more in tune with her
wants and needs than most men.
Oh, she's rung out.
That keeps happening.
Alright, if I said
I'd watch it
then I suppose that's what
I'm going to have to do.
- That's the spirit, Jen!
- Let's get it over with.
Now, keep an open mind.
I know the first show
was a bit "bare bones"
but I think you'll really enjoy
my new episode,
or 'webisode', if you prefer.
I don't prefer that.
No-one does.
Come on, come on. Sooner it
starts, sooner it's over.
Game Board.
Game. Game. Game.
- Game.
- Board.
Board.
Board. Board. Board.
Hello and welcome
to Games Board.
Today on the show, we have...
So, guys...
What's coming up on the show?
- Guys?
- I've...
I've been playing
'Ports of Essen',
a strategic trading game
where each player
takes the role of a Danish
fishing port merchant
in the 16th century.
And for a change of pace,
I've been looking at
the expansion to
'Textile Merchant',
Norfolk Edition'.
Two games by Rainer Kinitski?
Hold onto your hat,
it's going to be a bumpy...
Let's talk about components.
Shouldn't we do rules
before components?
Components won't make any sense
if we do it before the rules.
Don't forget to cut
this conversation.
- What?
- Don't let the program...
How long is this?
Even hearing it is bad.
I need to stop hearing it.
Sorry, Moss, I can't do it.
It's unbearable.
Where are you going?
- I'm jealous of your coffee.
- You literally can't watch it?
I literally can't watch it.
So what can we do
to make it better?
Well, I don't want to
say anything
that might hurt your feelings.
It's alright, I can take it,
Jen. I'm a big boy.
Well, as I say, it's slow.
It's so slow.
OK, good. It is a bit slow.
We can work on that.
And I guess the other thing
is that it's terrible.
It's slow and terrible.
If a friend asked me,
I'd say it's a slow,
terrible thing
I could only watch
for a minute.
Is this helpful?
Oh! So helpful!
God! "Slow. Terrible.
"Could only watch it
for a minute."
A lot to get our teeth
stuck into.
Let's see if I can help you
with anything else.
Erm, none of you are any good
in front of a camera.
- None of us. Yeah.
- You've got annoying voices.
The voices are a pain.
And I guess that's because
you haven't got any confidence.
No confidence.
If there's one thing you need,
it's confidence.
It is confidence. Absolutely.
Well, Jen, I can only
thank you, once again...
- And another thing...
- I'm not listening anymore!
- Douglas, you're incorrigible.
- I'm incorrigible?
You're Raymond Peterfellow,
owner of the finest lap-dancing
establishment in Soho.
If anyone's incorrigible it's
you, you perfumed porno vampire.
Perfumed porno
vampire. I like that.
So you're thinking of 500 of
these travelling across London?
- That's what I said.
- Sexy and classy.
And that's difficult
to pull off.
This will get people talking,
alright. Ha!
Consider me
one happy shareholder.
Right. Oh, big party coming up
on Thursday night
if you're up for it.
Damn, I'm supposed to be doing
'Secret Millionaire'.
Fuck it, I'll cancel.
I'll tell my assistant.
- Hi, Joan.
- Jen.
I'm not your assistant,
Mr Reynholm.
I want you to cancel
'Secret Millionaire'.
Not your assistant.
Wouldn't know who to call.
Just say anything.
Work your usual magic.
Not your assistant.
I am not your...
I thought this was the toilet.
Didn't this used to be toilets?
Yes. I moved my office here to
be closer to the ladies toilets.
Must get someone
to take that sign down.
What's wrong with you, Ross?
- Small mocha, please.
Okey-dokey.
Or...medium.
You know what? I've changed
my mind. I'll have a medium.
So you don't want a small one?
Small's fine. Small's good,
just as good, so I'll just...
Yes, that is what I'll have -
a small mocha, my little man.
My good man. My good little man.
OK, coming up.
Got it.
OK?
Fuck's sake.
Thank you for
the virgin gin and tonic.
I suppose you could
just call it 'tonic'.
Yes.
So, Ross, how goes it
in the world of computers?
Or PC world, if you will?
We're all very happy,
thank you, Mr Reynholm.
Very happy indeed.
Forget this 'we' malarky,
I'm talking to you, Ross.
Are you happy?
Very happy,
thank you, Mr Reynholm.
Look, I'm not your boss.
We're just a couple of guys
shooting the shit.
Now, tell me the truth.
Well, I suppose sometimes
I do feel I lack
a little confidence.
-- I know, it's silly.
No, I've just realised
what a funny voice you have.
Now, Ross, I'm going to
tell you something.
Confidence
is a confidence trick.
Look at me. What do you see?
A man who inherited his
father's successful business.
- Wasn't that successful.
- It was pretty successful.
A lot more successful than
it is now, that's for sure.
Alright, alright!
Just say the right thing.
Say the thing I want you to say.
- Say "a confident man".
- A confident man!
I wasn't always this way.
I was just like you, but then
I discovered the secret.
And Ross, I'm going to tell you
what that secret is,
but you must keep it
to yourself.
I will take my ears
to the grave.
Two words.
Women's slacks.
I'm sorry?
- Women's slacks?
- Yes.
I'm wearing women's slacks.
- You're wearing women's slacks?
- Yes.
That's nothing like what I
thought you were going to say.
- Is it not?
- It is not.
I thought you were going to
give me a book recommendation.
Book recommendation?
I can't read.
I don't know what it is,
but women's slacks give me
the confidence I need
to survive
in a tough business world.
They're lighter, airier and less
constricted than men's trousers,
and I'm pretty sure it doesn't
make me a transvestite.
Look at that shit. Look at it.
I can't...
How am I supposed to...
It looks like
he milked a cow over it.
You're so fussy about coffee.
It's very annoying.
It's ruined!
He ruined my coffee.
Don't just chuck it like that.
That fella shouldn't be allowed
to be a barista.
- Why not?
- Because he's too small, Jen.
He's clearly too small
to be a barista.
What?
You're being a bit of
a small person racist, Roy.
A small person racist?
That's not a thing.
You can't have tiny baristas,
Jen.
For God's sake,
the man works with steam!
I'm going to have to
have a word with him.
Have a word with him?
- That's right.
- About his height?
I think he'd appreciate
the feedback.
About his height?
That's not what people do, Roy.
Well, I'm not people, Jen,
and I think that's a good thing.
I'm not afraid to cut through
the bullshit.
I bet this is exactly what
Alice was talking about.
Autistic!
She said 'autistic'.
That's what happened.
- No, I don't think so.
- There's no artistic spectrum!
But she said I was...
Did she say it during
an argument, by any chance?
She did say it during a...
She did say it...
What was weird was, we were
having quite a big argument,
and then suddenly,
out of nowhere,
she paid me
that lovely compliment.
Hey, baby.
Oh, oh, good, good, yes.
Sure, yeah, I'd love to.
Yes, OK, well,
I'll see you there.
Wh... Why?
No, it's...
Hello? Alice?
- That was weird.
- What?
OK, so, what the hell is that?
So she tells me
that her grandfather died,
she wants me
to go to the funeral.
I say that I'd be delighted,
and then she hangs on me.
- Her grandfather's funeral?
- Yeah.
That's what you were
just talking about just there?
That's right.
You sounded like you were being
invited to Glastonbury.
Oh, funerals are sad.
- You did not sound sad.
- I wasn't concentrating!
Emotionally artistic? You're
emotionally colourblind.
Maybe I am emotionally
colourblind.
I was about to confront
that little man.
I was going to give him shit
about his height.
Glad you realise how
inappropriate that would be.
Yeah.
I'll just leave him a note.
- I'm here on purpose.
- Oh, yes.
I'm interested
in women's slacks.
I see.
I'd like... Sorry. Hot ear.
I'd like to buy a pair
of women's slacks.
For me, not for a woman.
Oh, yes, well,
that shouldn't be a problem.
I'm not trying to
look like a woman.
I understand.
I'm not a confident man.
Quite. Well, let's see
what we can do for you.
- I don't know about this.
- Oh, just ask them, Jen.
Me and Juan, we have a thing.
I don't want another
splishy-splashy coffee
from the teeny-tiny
coffee man!
Poor woman.
Don't give her money.
You're not supposed to do that.
I'm actually a person,
Roy, with human feelings.
- Oh.
- Oh!
- Oh?
- Whadya do that for?
- I'm sorry, I thought...
-- I don't know what to do.
- Here's £5. Do you want £5?
- I don't know if you want money.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Sorry!
- Arggh!
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- What happened?
Never mind, just go.
What do you think?
I think...
...you just sold a brother
some slacks.
Help! Help, get off me!
- Let go!
- You're a bully.
Need to save that old
woman, but I have no confidence.
Hey.
Thank you.
Red! Come on, no queue for you.
Come on.
- Hello, Juan.
- I'm with her.
It must be my birthday, I get
to see you twice so quick.
Yes, back again!
Same as usual, please.
And could I ask you
a huge favour
and ask you to make
Roy's coffee too?
I've been going on and on
about you.
And I like what I heard.
- Would that be OK? Do you mind?
- Anything for you, my sweet.
OK.
Slippery fingers.
- It's alright.
- It's not alright.
Look, it looks like me
with a beard.
I don't want this.
It's horrible.
Oh, God! Oh, my God!
- Why did you do that?!
- I didn't mean to!
I don't hate you.
None of this is on purpose.
What can I do?
Let me give you some money.
Here's £10. Oh, my God!
Huh?
- I'm not with her.
- Oi! Oi!
Jesus!
- Did you write this comment?
- No.
You've got a problem
with smaller people.
I don't have a problem with
small people, OK? I don't.
I just don't want you
making my coffee.
Because you're bad at it.
You're bad at making coffee.
You're too small. You're too
small to make good coffee.
- You know what? Up yours.
- No...
- Little man, watch out!
It's being called
the viral video of the year.
A woman throws her coffee
onto a tramp
and then a man has an argument
with a small barista.
You're just too small!
The barista
goes to cross the road
and is hit by a van
with breasts.
The woman who's been dubbed
by various online commentators
as Coffee Tramp Toss Bitch
has not been identified,
while the man known as
Small Person Racist was also...
Small people are not a race.
This isn't 'Game of Thrones'.
They're actually calling me
a bitch on the news.
What the hell happened there?
- How did you find out?
- Weekly surveillance report.
What's going on, Joan?
I expect better
from my assistant.
I'm not your assistant.
My name isn't Joan.
What's your beef
with the homeless?
I don't have any homeless beef.
Ah, so it's women you hate.
Well, that I can understand.
Whoa. You record our emails
and tape our phone calls?
Alright, dry your eyes, Bono.
If you've nothing to hide,
you've nothing to fear.
It wasn't my fault,
Mr Reynholm.
I would never throw coffee
over a homeless woman.
And I would never
abuse a small person.
Certainly not enough to make
a van with tits hit him.
Although I suppose
I sort of did.
I sort of did my one too.
Frustrating that we did
both of our things.
Yes, it is.
Alright, spare me.
I was young once.
But if this gets out,
this could deeply damage
Reynholm Industries' ability
to make that product
that we make.
What do you want us
to do, Mr Reynholm?
Don't do anything.
Stay out of trouble,
and remember,
there are places
lower than the basement.
Stop worrying, Jen. Nobody can
make us out in that video.
It's just like early footage
of happy slapping. Just relax.
I can't relax. It's alright
for you. I have plans.
I want to get up there.
I will not be a social piranha.
A what, now?
- Jen, take a look at this.
- What is it?
- The new-look 'Game Board'.
-200,000 views?
I know. It's a bit different.
- Check it out. Game Board.
- Shut the fridge. It's...
- Game Board.
----- Game Board.
Say what?
Wow! You all
seem different somehow.
Yes. We're all wearing
women's trousers.
Oh. Right.
Hey, what's going on?
It's G-G-G-G-Game Board.
- He's...
- Newton Sinclair.
- This guy's...
- Roger Booth.
And I guess
I'm still Maurice Moss.
Are you wearing
the trousers now?
I couldn't wear them all the
time. I'd have a heart attack.
No, they're safely locked away
in my fortress of solitude.
It's funny - when I wear them,
I'm a dynamo,
a young Leonard Kravitz, people
hanging off my every word.
And then as soon as
I take them off
I'm just back to being
the same...
She's gone, hasn't she?
She's gone.
- She went quite a while ago.
- Yeah.
- Oh, Michael Bublé's here!
- No, no, it's a funeral, Moss.
I have to go to this funeral
for Alice's grandfather,
and I'm not looking forward
to it.
Funerals are pain in the crack.
Even in the best of
circumstances they're no picnic,
but now I've got Alice on my
arse like the emotion police.
So I'm going to have to look
convincingly sad
for the majority of the day.
Eugh.
She's not going to expect me
to cry, is she?
- No.
- What if she does?!
I can't cry on cue.
What do I do then?
Do what I do
when I need to cry.
Use a mild pepper spray
solution.
Now, that makes sense, see?
That makes more sense
than having to feel something.
Do you have
any of that stuff here?
Why do you think
we have a mini-fridge?
Good evening.
- You've got quite a lot of it.
- I suppose I have made a lot.
And what's in here?
Just Tabasco, wasabi
and a bit of tear gas.
Those sound like bad things
to put in your eyes.
It's extremely mild.
It's mainly water.
- I'll take it as a last resort.
- As a last resort.
In case I find myself
out of my emotional depth.
- There you go.
- Alright. Thanks, Moss.
-'Bye.
Oh, don't forget
to add the water.
- Oh, poor Pip Pop.
- Sorry, what?
Pip Pop.
We always called him Pip Pop
because he was so short.
All of my family on that side
are really short.
Is that right?
Ohhh. Oh, Alice. Shh.
Oh!
- Roy, are you alright?
- Holy...
- Yeah, it just really hurts.
- Oh, Roy.
- Oh, it hurts.
- I know. I know.
Oh, Christ,
why is this happening?
So will we ever find out
just who this person was?
Unfortunately,
with current technology,
we can't de-pixelate the
picture, so it's very unlikely
we'll ever find out
the identity
of this dreadful ginger cow
- Christ. What the f...
- Oh, are you still crying?
I don't seem to be able to stop.
What's happening now?
One of the pallbearers
wasn't able to make it.
- Oh.
- I know this is a bit weird.
Do you mind stepping in?
- I'm happy to.
- Thank you.
I mean, I'm sadly happy to,
yeah.
That's fine.
Hi, thanks so much
for helping us out.
No problemo. Hey. Hi there.
Hello. Oh, there's another one.
Hi. Are these the
other pallbearers?
- Yeah.
- Oh, God.
So you guys and me, we're going
to carry the coffin together?
Yes.
We're going to put the casket
on our collective shoulders
and walk in a straight line
with it?
No, it didn't go well, Jen.
It didn't go well at all.
I mean, thanks for asking,
but no, it wasn't a success.
It wasn't a successful funeral
for me.
Didn't have
the required gravitas.
- Gravitas? No, no.
- It wasn't very dignified.
It wasn't dignified at all, Jen!
If I had to pick a word
to describe Pip Pop's final
journey to the grave,
it would be 'funny'.
It was so funny, Jen.
Of course, I tried not to laugh
and I tried to put
other things in my head,
but every step that we took
was a fresh reminder
of just how funny
the whole thing was!
- You didn't laugh, did you?
- I laughed my hole off!
I can't believe
she's still with you.
I suppose, but, I mean, I'm
hanging on by a thread, Jen.
I'll get through it as long as
nothing else bad happens.
There's the phone now.
The new footage has led
to the pair being identified -
Jen Barber and Roy Trenneman,
both employees
at Reynholm Industries.
What the hell
were you thinking?
I told you to keep a low
profile and you do it again!
No, no, no, no, no, it's new
footage, Mr Reynholm.
Bum your excuses!
Reynholm Industries
has a reputation to uphold.
We're not News International,
for Christ's sake!
I'm going to have to do 'Secret
pissing Millionaire' now
just to undo your damage!
And I'm missing out
on a massive tit party!
And you're no longer
my assistant.
I'm furious.
And I'll tell you
something else,
when I return from the estate,
it's...
...for you.
-- Oh! Oh!
Hey, baby.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Yeah, no, absolutely.
Alright, OK. Bye-bye.
- She left you?
- She did. Yeah.
As the identities
of Coffee Toss Tramp Bitch
and Small Person Racist
are finally revealed,
we at Channel 4 News ask,
"What the hell
is wrong with people?"
I've got a lot of new
followers on Chitter.
- Loads more followers, yeah.
- They're all very abusive.
- They wish we were dead.
- Wait.
- What?
- Chitter.
We can use Chitter
to explain ourselves.
Yeah.
Chitter is the perfect place
to explain a complex situation.
"I didn't mean to throw coffee
on that woman.
"I didn't know she was there.
"I went back to try
and find her, but..."
- Too many characters.
Got it. "Hate the homeless?
"And I suppose
I hate women too.
"LOL." Send.
Whoa. You didn't
just send that, did you?
- Yes.
- That didn't sound so good.
People get the sense of it.
That's the thing about Chitter.
It's best if you're
conversational, off the cuff.
Here it is.
Oh. You didn't put a question
mark after the first sentence.
You don't need to use
proper grammar on Chitter, Roy.
What you've chitted here,
Jen, is
"Hate the homeless and I suppose
I hate women too. LOL."
Phew!
I'm glad all that's over.
Ohhhhh.
And then
laughs about it on Chitter.
You're too small.
You're just too small!
You're too small,
too small, too small...
...which then leads to him
being hit by a van with tits.
And now Anonymous are after us.
Well, that's just ideal.
Oh, a bunch of nerds sitting
at their computer,
what can they do?
We pissed off the internet, Jen.
The internet
is coming to get us!
Well, let's get it
before it gets us.
What are you...
Oh, I don't want
Anonymous after me.
I'm in Anonymous!
I think.
Let's hide it!
- What?
- The internet!
Oh.
Because we told you that
that was the internet?
Yes.
And we never told you
that it wasn't the internet?
- No.
- Well, the thing is, Jen...
That's not the internet.
What's Jen doing
with the internet?
- We're not doing that.
- Oh!
Crickets!
Right, don't be scared, yeah?
We're all friends here.
- Tell Dougie your story.
- OK, but who is he again?
I'm just your average
social worker.
Yes, just in the area
having a look around.
Please, just pretend
I'm not here.
Do you ever have anyone come
round and help you and stuff?
Grandad, sometimes,
but he's hardly around.
- What about your dad?
- He's never around either.
Sorry, I have to stop you there.
I must take this.
Reynholm.
What? Well, increase the bid.
I don't care what I said
the ceiling was.
I want that artwork by Madonna.
No, 22 million is the minimum,
but I'm happy to go to 50.
In fact, make 50
the new minimum. Yes, yes.
I can't talk right now.
I'm doing 'Secret Millionaire'.
That's very sad.
Do you want to shut up? We're
filming 'Secret Millionaire'.
Check your privilege.
How am I finding it so far?
To be honest with you,
it's not as God-awful
as I thought it would be.
The people have been terribly
nice, actually quite clean.
And I have been invited
to a party this evening.
The last party I ever went to
was when EIton John's dog
had a baby.
I tell a lie.
The last party I went to was
when Conrad Black got arrested.
Conrad Black, who's that?
Oh, no-one, just an old friend.
Let's get in there!
Yeah, sure.
So I thought with 'Game Board's
increased viewership,
perhaps it would be a good place
to put my side of the story
and show the world
I'm not the monster
I'm currently supposed to be.
- Boo! Boo!
- Could you not boo me, please?
And that is a horrible T-shirt.
So the question
everyone's asking -
Jen Barber, do you hate women?
Oh.
- Thank you, Jen Barber.
- No...
Coming up, what was it like
to be a 14th-century
grain merchant?
- I don't know if that was clear.
- Sorry, it's these trousers.
They make me want to move
onto the next item.
It's better broadcasting,
and the slacks know it!
- Coming up...
- Stop saying "coming up".
I don't know
if I made my point!
Oh, gosh!
Oh!
Oh, gosh.
Richmond, do you work here
or not?
I don't get paid,
but I like to come in.
So that Goth 2 Boss thing
didn't work out?
Does it look like
it worked out?
Anyway, how have you guys been?
Everyone thinks
I'm a misogynist,
Roy lost his girlfriend because
he's emotionally colourblind
and Moss is wearing trousers
that make him good at telly.
Any gossip?
So, what's going on with you?
Oh, you know, keeping busy.
Voice-over work mainly.
Really? How did that happen?
Someone just noticed
I had a beautiful voice.
Oh, Richmond.
Things aren't going well at all.
Just get in there.
It's just not the same
when you guys aren't together.
Anyway, if you want me,
you know where I am.
I don't, though, Richmond.
Don't lurk!
Where did he go?
Where did who go?
Does it ever seem to you that
the things that happen to us
are sort of...strange?
How so, Roy?
Well, remember when I had to
pretend to be disabled
and I ended up in Manchester?
That wasn't a normal thing
to happen, was it?
Or when you ended up
spending the night
in that arcade machine.
That was odd.
I suppose those were
unusual events.
And this is strange.
What's happening to us
right now is strange, isn't it?
Well, at least
it'll all be over soon.
Douglas is bound to fire us
when he gets back.
Come on, guys, this isn't us.
Are we just going to sit here
and take it?
What do we normally do
when we get into a scrape?
We normally make things worse
and worse and then it ends.
- No, we stick together.
- That doesn't sound like us.
Don't know where
you're getting that from.
Who are we? Who are we?
I want to hear you say it!
- We're the IT...
- We're the IT Department.
You're goddamn right we are!
- Are those women's slacks?
- Yes.
This is exactly what
I'm talking about.
Let's get into a car
and cruise around.
How do we get into a car?
Smash a window. Great idea!
That's the one!
I'm such an idiot.
I've got a robot hand!
Hang on a second.
This is my car!
Oh, shit. Whoa. It's alright,
everyone, be cool.
I'll handle this. Take that.
It's alright, officer, I'm
doing 'Secret Millionaire'.
Come on, come on, come on,
people. What's going on?
Come on, come on,
come on, people.
How long has he been wearing
the trousers?
- He won't take them off.
- OK, come on, come on, come on.
What's going on?
We don't know what's happening.
To every problem there's a
solution. What's our problem?
Everyone thinks I'm a cow
who hates women.
You're a cow, that's right.
A terrible cow. Women, OK.
Roy, hurt me.
The woman I love thinks
that I hate small people.
Small people. Thank you, Roy.
I'll probably die alone in
front of computer pornography.
I'll just draw a sad face.
OK, so what do women
and small people both like?
What do they both like?
- Chairs.
- Films.
I really don't know.
I'll tell you.
It's just they seem like
very different groups.
Not being attacked.
They both love
not being attacked.
Well, I can't speak
for small people, obviously,
but as a woman, I certainly
like not being attacked.
Where are you going with this,
Moss?
I'll tell you exactly
where I'm going with this, Roy.
I'm saying we use this brief
window, while Douglas is away,
to produce a pepper spray
solution for small women
using that stuff
I gave Roy earlier.
That sounds really weird.
Jen Barber,
not a hater of women,
but their defender,
their champion.
I love it now!
And I can do
a massive presentation.
A self-defence pepper spray
for small women
suits my purposes also!
It will show Alice that I care
and, as a woman
with small relatives,
she's sure to come to
Jen's presentation.
You know, when I first
stocked that mini-fridge
with pepper spray solution,
I thought I'd made too much,
but only now do I realise
that I'd made exactly the right
amount for our current purposes.
It almost seems like
it's too good an idea.
You see what we can do
when we work together?
With my business acumen...
- My scientific know-how...
- And I'm also here.
- We can do anything!
- Yeah!
I need a trouser break.
You coming, Roy?
I can't seem to get the wording
of this speech to Alice right.
- You're doing a speech?
- Yeah.
I need to show her that I'm
not emotionally colourblind.
I'm a very sensitive human man,
and she needs to know that.
Oooh, what's a more romantic
word for 'knockers'?
A more romantic word?
Come on, guys.
Let's protect women.
- I'll meet you up there.
- Good luck.
Thanks.
'Eartha Kitts'!
Right, is everything ready?
Yeah, well,
I've got the posters up
and I've put gift bags with
pepper spray beside each chair.
Now, I think it was
a masterstroke
to put the spray
in these elegant bottles.
Why not look stylish
while you defend yourself?
Something's bothering me,
though.
Are we missing something
that's very obviously wrong
with this idea?
I really don't think so.
Oh, look, here comes everyone.
Perfect!
Hello and welcome to this
very special presentation
for women by a woman, me,
a woman, who loves women.
By your seats you'll find
a gift bag, and in that gift bag
you'll find
our very exciting new product.
- No, don't do that.
- No, you're not supposed to...
Alice! Yes! I have some things
I have to say to you!
- No, I need to go!
- No, you are going nowhere.
Now, I know in the past
that you have accused me
of being emotionally
colourblind.
- Arggh!
- Shut up and listen.
But now I've changed.
My sight is perfect.
Now I know what was wrong
with the idea.
And with your sweet lips and
of course your lovely bangers,
I know you're the one for me.
- I'm in terrible pain!
- Me too, Alice, me too!
But that ends now. It ends now.
That could not
have gone better!
No, no, Roy,
that didn't go well at all.
Oh, right, because we're
going to lose our jobs.
- Arrgh!
Mr Reynholm!
So that's the thing - I gave
the boy the can of lager,
so technically I'm guilty
of corrupting a minor.
So it's the reason why
I bought the tramp uniform,
and I've had to
make myself scarce.
So you need somewhere
to hide out?
Yeah, somewhere off-piste.
- Where no-one will find you.
- Bottom of the world.
You can use our office
if you like.
Whoa!
Well, I'll need someone to take
care of business upstairs.
We're not doing anything.
Well, this is perfect.
My wonderful assistant, Joan,
and her two friends... Ross.
I'm going to go and piss around
on the internet,
but actually,
I'll need some food.
I've already eaten
one of the toys in here.
Did he just say
what I think he said?
I wasn't really listening.
Is this... Is what's
happening good now?
- Is this good?
- Yes, it's a very good outcome.
Oh, my God! I think we've come
out on top. I can't believe it.
We've come out on top.
Jen Barber.
- Oh, I forgot about you.
- Oh, God, that's impressive.
They're actually watching us.
Hey, mate, am I in Anonymous?
Silence, Small Person Racist.
Greetings, Jen Barber.
This is your sentence.
You've been found guilty
of the most appalling lack
of basic human kindness
and decency.
-- Come in.
Shush, you!
- Peter, what are you doing?
- Shut up!
- You've been in here for hours.
- I'm doing something. Go away!
Peter, your mother and I
are worried about you.
You're in my room! Get out!
It's a beautiful day. You should
get off this computer.
No, I'm not!
Who is this?
Are these your friends?
I'm sorry, Peter can't play
anymore. He's coming outside.
You said I could stay
here for as long as I wanted.
We said that
you had to come out.
You said I could use
the computer
for two hours every day
as long as I ate my dinner
and did my homework.
I have! What are you doing
taking it away from me?
I have earned my right. I know
my rights, Mum and Dad.
No! No!
This internet's not
working. I can't connect.
Just try
turning it off and on again.
Thanks, Ross.
Reynholm Industries
is changing.
New opportunities, new faces,
a new direction.
A better workplace environment.
Exciting new products.
An inclusive hiring policy.
I am sounding happy.
- Can you be a bit more...
- This is me being happy.
- Just be a bit more...
- I'm being up-beat.
No, I just want you to speak...
Ah, forget it, let's just stop.