So, how much are you asking for?
Oh, nothing,
just take whatever you want.
I just don't want to start cluttering up
the place with old stuff, you know.
That's kind of what
this new place is all about.
I just want to totally reinvent myself.
From this moment on,
everything is going to be different.
Hello, IT, have you tried
turning it off and on again?
I did it! I did it! I've been accepted!
- No!
- What's going on?
I've been accepted!
I applied and they said yes!
Who said yes?
What are you talking about?
Moss, you're shaking!
Consonant, please.
- B.
- And a vowel, please.
And lastly, A.
And here's the Countdown clock.
All right, let's see what we've got.
Jeremy?
Six.
- And Maurice?
- Nine.
- Jeremy, what's your six?
-"Tenant."
- And Maurice?
- It actually already is a word.
"Tnetennba."
Good heavens, really?
Could you use it in a sentence for us?
"Good morning. That's a nice tnetennba."
Someone reminded me earlier,
you haven't yet got a word
less than eight letters long.
It's quite extraordinary.
You really do look like you're on your
way to winning that Countdown teapot!
No offence, Jeremy.
Who are you?
- You want me to do your windows, mate?
- What?
- I'm working.
- What? I can't understand you.
- Right on, mate.
- No! No, no!
-- Stop cleaning my windows!
I want to go to the toilet.
I don't know what you're saying.
The window in front,
the window in back...
Yes, yes, yes. Okey dokey.
I can't understand what you're saying.
- Leave my bike for a few...
- Okay, then. All right. Bye-bye.
Okay. What are you doing?
-- Why are you bringing the bike inside?
What? No! Where are you going?
Where are you going?
Why do I have your bike?
And then, when he leaves, he just
leaves all of his stuff in my flat.
What stuff?
You know, all his
window-cleaning bollocks!
The ladder, the bike, everything.
It's still there!
- What, in your flat?
- Yeah, he never came back!
How did he even get in?
Well, he was very persuasive.
I think.
Well, I don't know how to get
in touch with this guy.
His stuff is cluttering up my hallway.
I've had to start putting these up.
My mum always says
you should never open the door.
- What do you mean?
- An unopened door is a happy door.
So we never answer ours
when someone knocks.
- What, so you all just sit there?
- Yes.
So the doorbell goes
and you all just sit there
-until the person goes away?
- Yes.
What if it's important?
What if it's good news?
This is London, Jen.
It's not someone with cake.
Unless that cake is made
of dog poo and knives!
Laters. I'm going to zone out
at the Heads of Department meeting.
I thought you were
trying to avoid those.
There's only so many times I can say
there's a RAM emergency.
Hello?
Yes?
Hello. Can I come in?
- Why?
- What?
Why do you want to come in?
Isn't this the Heads
of Department meeting?
Every Monday and Friday?
Or has it changed?
No, no, yes, it is, yes, um...
You've missed a few though, haven't you?
Yeah, there was a RAM emergency.
The office had too much RAM.
Okay, well, you see, the nature of
the meetings has changed somewhat
and it wouldn't be fair on you.
There'd be a lot of catching up to do.
Okay.
Okay, thanks, Jen!
They don't want me!
They don't want me at the Monday-Friday!
I thought you hated those meetings.
I did hate those meetings.
Until they didn't want me
at those meetings.
And now I love those meetings.
Five minutes, Mr Moss.
Thanks, Phil.
A fan of tiny biscuits.
You are full of surprises.
Please, don't let me stop you.
I like a man with appetite.
It's what got you this far.
Sorry, do I know you?
They call me Prime.
I had another name once.
I no longer go by it. Harold Tong.
That's right.
I won year 16 of Countdown.
Yes, it was I who won
the 16th Countdown teapot.
The teapot we all crave.
You crave it, too!
Your eyes betray you!
Uh-huh.
He has spirit, this one!
But do you have the spirit
to become an ultimate champion?
I wonder.
Do you want to get a photo together
or something?
I came only to give you this.
What is it?
Roy?
Jesus! Alistair, hey!
- Long time no see!
- Yeah.
Uh, Roy and I were at college together.
Yeah. Wow, you are looking great!
Thanks.
So what are you up to these days?
What am I up to? Wow. Big question.
Um, I'm the head writer
for Shotgun games.
- Do you know them?
- Yeah!
Wow! Really?
I play Shotgun games all the time.
- They're brilliant.
- Oh, thank you.
Wow, that is so cool.
Hey, you just won an award, right?
Yes.
Well, see you soon, Roy.
Don't ask me what I'm doing,
you arrogant twat.
Sorry, I'm not sure
I'm in the right place.
Oh, you're in the right place, Mr Moss.
Welcome to Eight Plus.
You came! I'm glad!
That's Roger Black
and that's Steven Pawlin.
You know your ex-Countdown winners!
Why are they all here?
Why, for someone who knows
how to add and subtract
and multiply and divide lots of numbers
to get one other number,
you're not so good at putting
two and two together, are you?
This is Eight Plus!
An exclusive club for those gifted few
who make it through
to eight episodes of Countdown.
And you are our newest member.
Oh, isn't that nice?
Thanks for letting me know, Linda.
All right. All right, bye.
Does it not outrage you, Roy,
as a member of this IT department,
that I, your head, is not being
represented at the Monday-Friday?
Couldn't give a shit.
My neighbour just called.
Turns out that window-washing Willy
from West Gibberish
is not now going to be able to pick up
his window-cleaning bric-a-brac.
Why not?
Oh, he was hit by a car or something.
It's just my luck!
You shouldn't have agreed
to mind it for him in the first place.
Oh, thanks, Jen. That's really helpful.
That's really good advice.
That's exactly what I'll do,
in the past, when it happens again,
last week.
I have to give it back to him!
It can't just live in my hallway!
Don't give a shit!
No, no. Oh, look, no!
No... Alistair!
I'm not a window cleaner!
I'm not a... Alistair!
Alistair! I'm not a window cleaner!
I'm not a window cleaner! Alistair!
I'm not a window cleaner!
All right, something weird
is going on in that room.
They're wearing dressing gowns.
Roy, will you listen to me?
I don't have to listen to you.
I'm not married to you.
I've got a lot on my mind
right now, Jen.
This bloke thinks I'm a window cleaner.
Bloke I went to college with,
he's doing amazingly.
The creature he was with!
And he thinks
that I am a window cleaner!
A window cleaner!
What's wrong with that?
It's a noble profession.
If your last profession
was cleaning balls!
- Google him.
- I've tried. He has no online presence.
Apparently, people were being rude
to him so he suspended all his accounts.
He's not on Friendface,
he's not on Chitter...
Listen...
How do people expect you
to track them down
if they maintain no online presence?
You have both asked
and answered that question.
What do you think is going on up there?
Is this Meeting Room 5?
You know, they soundproofed that
a few weeks ago?
Really? What's that all about?
Douglas said it was
for super-secret meetings.
But I want to go
to super-secret meetings!
I can't believe I might be missing
super-secret meetings!
But the dressing gowns!
Why are they wearing dressing gowns?
- Orgies.
- No!
Maybe they're getting some kind of
executive massage treatment
for being brilliant!
Do you think they're getting massages?
If they're getting massages, I think
my human rights are being abused
by them not letting me in.
Why don't you wear a towel,
hang around the door
and see if they let you in?
I have my dignity, thank you, Moss.
No. Hang on, that might just work!
Oh!
I can't believe you've joined
a swanky club. It's so showbizzy!
Roy, the people here see me
in a certain way.
It's perhaps not the way
I've been seen outside of the club.
I'd just like you not to, you know,
mention it in any way, or, you know...
Sure. Yeah. No problem.
Oh.
Hello, Terence.
Glass of milk. Straight up.
- Prime?
- Ribena for me.
Roy?
Uh, I'll have a beer. Thank you.
Alcohol-free beer, surely?
No.
- Get him what he wants.
- But...
Just get him what he wants.
I'll have to go out.
Can somebody mind the bar?
No, no. You know what? It's fine.
Um... I'll just...
I shouldn't really be drinking
during lunch.
- I'll just have a Coke.
- It's fine.
Will I see you tonight?
Not now, Ivana.
Did you have sex with that lady?
If you call that mindless,
animalistic rutting sex,
then yes, I suppose we did.
That sounds like sex.
Countdown groupies are the most
sexually voracious of all groupies.
And the most beautiful.
I hear someone likes drinking beer.
This is a private booth, Negative One.
The name!
This is a private club, Word.
Word! True dat! True dat, innit?
My name is Word here.
Roy, please.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry, Negative One.
Heard you been catching
some nice letters.
I get the same letters as everyone else.
Good when they fall
in the right order, though, innit?
Steady, gentlemen.
Boom!
Don't mind him.
Negative One was quite proud
of being our best speller
until Moss came along.
Ah! Our drinks.
Can I just say,
I am having a great time.
Hey, yo, turn the music off!
Turn the music off!
Uh-oh, what's he up to?
Maybe our new champion would like
to test his skills out on the street.
He's challenging you
to a game of Street Countdown!
You cannot accept. It's too dangerous.
Well, what do you say?
Or is you worried you is going to show
yourself up in front of your girlfriend?
He's calling Roy your girlfriend.
Within the walls of Eight Plus,
that's a definite dis.
You're lucky my "girlfriend"
has gone to the toilet.
Is you gonna answer me or what?
No! We promised those days were over!
No more unlicensed
Street Countdown battles!
I didn't "aks" you. I "aksed" him.
Well?
What is Street Countdown?
It's more or less the same
as normal Countdown,
except we play it on the street.
Doesn't sound that dangerous.
It can get quite cold.
- I always wear thermals.
- Ah, then you're probably fine.
Hey, I is still standing here.
What do you say, newbie?
I came here to drink milk and kick ass.
And I've just finished my milk.
Welcome to Street Countdown!
Ooh!
First rule of Street Countdown
is that you really must try and tell
as many people as possible about it.
It's a rather fun game, and the more
people we tell about it, the better.
What the...
Where is everyone? Hello?
Hello? Moss?
Ivana?
Hello?
Hello in there!
Oh, for... Ooh.
Oh, hey! Hey, mate! Mate!
Um, could you do me a favour?
So, do you just do big windows
or do you do call-outs?
What, do you think I'm going to
come round and do your house?
No. No. Didn't think that.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, hey!
Alistair! Alistair! It's me.
Alistair! I'm not a window cleaner!
What?
I'm not a window cleaner!
What? I've got to go!
I'm... I'm not a window cleaner!
Oh, that bloke,
he thinks I'm a bloody window cleaner!
Not that there's...
It's a noble profession.
Is this as fast as this goes?
Consonant.
Vowel.
Vowel. Boom!
I'll take a further consonant.
Consonant. You get me?
I'll take a vowel this time.
I'll have what he's having. Vowel.
I'll have another consonant.
Give me one of those sweet,
sweet consonants, you get me?
I'll take a consonant,
plain and simple, thank you.
I'll take an even sweeter vowel.
I'll take a regular vowel, please.
Yeah, I think... I think that's
probably enough letters, yeah?
Eighteen letters!
I've never seen so many.
He is the one.
- What happened to you...?
- Shh!
This is the longest word yet
on Street Countdown.
Unlike normal Countdown,
you see, what happens...
I don't care.
Negative One?
Twelve.
Ooh!
Moss?
Sixteen.
Your word, Negative One?
"Enormousness."
I shall give my answer, if I may,
in the form of a joke.
This is most irregular!
What do you call Negative One
sitting alone in an empty room?
I don't know. What do you call Negative
One sitting alone in an empty room?
"Overnumerousness!"
Gyles?
Yes, that is a word!
And the joke does make sense!
Okay, let's go!
- Oh, yes!
- Oh, shit.
Five, six, seven...
Ah, Jen, you've joined us!
Yes, yes, I have.
You're not really dressed for it.
Thought I'd wear normal clothes
and work up a real sweat.
Hardcore! And there's me thinking
you didn't have it in you.
Right, now let's take it to the max!
Five, six, seven, eight!
Hey! Hey, Alistair!
Oh, God, I can't believe I got you!
How you doing?
Yeah, no, it's Roy. Yeah, hello.
Listen, Alistair, I just wanted to say,
I'm not a window cleaner.
No, no, I work in IT!
Yeah, yeah, with computers and all that.
Macs? Uh, no,
I really just work with Windows.
Hello?