Morning, beautiful.
Course. I'll send someone up
as soon as I can, OK? Bye.
Ow! Oh!
You're very late. It's been crazy
down here, we've had a call.
- Sorry.
- Oh, God.
Are you all right?
- Are you poorly?
- No, it's just... it's just a bad bra.
It's the only one I had handy this morning
and it's really terrible.
It's pinching into my sides and the
straps are digging into my shoulders.
All that and it's not even giving
my breasts proper support! It's killing me.
Oh, Moss.
Moss, Moss.
- Oh, I'm sorry, are you OK?
- What happened?
Sometimes I forget
I'm not just working with other women.
No, it's my fault, I really ought to be able to
listen to a woman talking about bras without...
Ohhh! Moss, Moss.
Oh, hello, good morning, here I am.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah... Sorry.
The first time, I-I wasn't expecting you
to start talking about bras
and then, the second time, it came as a bit of
a surprise to hear myself talking about them.
- It's been a roller coaster.
- Why don't you have a lie-down in there?
- Morning.
God, I feel rough.
- Good stag?
- Yeah. Good, you know. Standard stag.
I may have got a little bit drunk
towards the end there.
Oh, well, what kind of celebration would it
be if you didn't pass out at some point?
Yeah, thank God nobody noticed.
How do you know I passed out?
I'm a bit psychic sometimes,
and I bet you came straight from
the party as well, didn't you?
That's easy, I'm wearing the same clothes.
Roy, I was trying to remember
how that song goes, "The Locomotion".
- Do you remember that song?
- Course I remember.
- How's it go again?
- You know it, you must know it.
- ♪ Everybody is doing a brand-new dance
- No, no, no, no, no, no. It's...
♪ Everybody's doing
a brand-new dance now
♪ Come on, baby,
do the locomotion
It is a funny song.
- You all right there?
- Yep. It's just a bad bra.
- Ah.
- Right, I have got to go.
Heads of department meeting.
After last week's fiasco,
I need to make a good impression.
We didn't think you'd believe us.
I mean, if you'd just stopped
to think about it for one second
you'd have realised that it wasn't true.
I don't think that's true.
With all due respect, John,
I am head of IT.
And I have it on good authority.
If you type "google" into Google,
you can break the internet,
so, please, no one try it, even for a joke.
It's not a laughing matter.
You can break the internet.
You don't know what those meetings
are like. They are murder.
It does you no harm
to look a little foolish from time to time.
Roy, there's something
I should let you know.
What?
Stephanie called earlier. Douglas needs
someone to take a look at his computer.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Get Moss to do it.
Oh, Moss isn't feeling too well, and besides,
of the two of you, you're the expert.
"The Ordinary Boys".
Where do they get these crazy names?
Entrare!
Hi, Mr Reynholm. Roy, IT.
Uh, my computer's...
my computer's broken.
Wow, I have to say
that's a really wild look.
You know, things are moving just so fast,
I can't keep up.
First the Ordinary Boys, and now this.
- Sh-should I check it out?
- Great, yeah.
- Let's get started, shall we?
- What?
What needs my expertise?
You... you did say you were with IT,
didn't you?
Yeah.
Come on, Mr Reynholm, while I'm down here,
I may as well get to work.
OK, I'm gonna move over here.
Sure.
Ah, I can see
why you've been having problems.
See, this isn't actually a computer.
It's a briefcase.
- Excellent.
- I'll have one sent up.
I admire you, Roy.
You've got the guts
to stand up for what you believe in.
OK. See you, then.
Roy...
Good luck.
Which means that we now have the cleanest
toilets of any legal department in London.
- Thank you.
- Well done, James.
You managed to speak for eight minutes
without actually saying anything.
- Oh, I think that, um...
- What? What?
No, nothing.
Who's next? Right, Jen.
OK, what's going on down in Middle-earth?
Thank you, John,
and prepare to be astonished,
because I have discovered four ways
to increase our online visibility
without spending a single penny.
Number one...
Oh!
Uh... Ha! 'Scuse me, sorry.
Number one... Aah!
Number 0... Aaah!
- The bloody thing!
- For God's sake!
Bloody thing.
Bloody pain in the arse.
I'm a woman.
Ohh!
It's really pinching my sides.
The straps are digging into my shoulders.
Eh, Moss, look - I'm a woman.
And I love you, Moss.
I love you.
The straps
are digging into my shoulders.
They're not giving my breasts
proper support... proper support...
proper support...
Hang on a second.
I've done it.
I've done it!
- Hello.
- Hello, Jen.
Who is this?
That's not important right now.
Well, it says "Moss" on my phone.
Yes, all right, it's me.
Why are you disguising your voice?
Because if someone is listening in
on this conversation,
I don't want them to know my identity.
- But they know now.
- Yes, thanks.
So why don't you use
your normal voice now?
It's attached to the phone
and I'd have to hang it up again...
Look, can you just listen to me?
Why don't you just come in
and speak to me?
Oh, you're...
- You're ruining everything.
- What do you want, Moss?
Take your top off, Jen.
- Sorry?
- You heard me. Take your top off.
- What's this all about, anyway?
- You'll see.
- Is this another one of your inventions?
- Maybe.
What was the last one? Oh, yeah.
A ladder to help moths
escape from the bath.
- How was that useful?
- How's that not useful?
- Moths don't get stuck in baths.
- Yes. They. Do.
Even if that were true,
it's just not in their nature
to learn how to use a ladder.
They have wings.
When a moth thinks about
travelling vertically upwards...
a ladder
is just the last thing they would think of.
Moss, I don't like to be negative about it,
but everything you invent is worthless.
Ah, well, prepare to put mustard on those
words, for you will soon be consuming them,
along with this slice of humble pie
that comes direct from the oven of shame,
set at gas mark egg on your face.
I sort of forget
what I was talking about.
Ah, here's Jen. Oh, that's it, it's a bra.
I've made a brilliant bra.
How are ye?
Is it, uh... comfortable?
This is possibly the most comfortable bra
I have ever worn.
Donning clothes over a bad bra is like
building a house without laying a foundation.
It's just a false economy,
and an ill-fitting bra could well ruin your
otherwise painstakingly selected ensemble.
- Wow, you really know your stuff.
- Thank you.
- Google?
- Yeah.
Jen, Roy, bad bras are more
than just a nuisance, they're a menace.
Years of wearing a bad bra can contribute
to upper back and shoulder pain.
It can even lead to headaches.
So, what makes this bra different?
- It can never go bad.
- What do you mean?
Tiny elements of fisilca rub together
to prevent the fabric from resting too long
in any one position.
It's a living bra.
The effect would be rather like
having a large pair of man's hands
holding the breasts in position.
But the bra will go bad.
All bras go bad.
Not this one, Jen. But don't take
my word for it - take it out for a spin.
- So what's it called?
- I call it.. the Abracadabra!
- You are kidding me.
- No.
You're really going on Dragons' Den?
I've got an interview today
with the producers at the BBC.
Oh, that is just huge.
You're gonna be on telly.
I know, but you've got to keep this
under your respective hats.
So if anyone asks for me,
my name is Stephen Jennel.
- Why Stephen Jennel?
- If my calculations are correct,
this could be the only bra
a woman need ever buy.
Do you know what Playtex would do to me
if they knew about the Abracadabra?
- What would they do?
- They would kill me, Jen.
I don't know if they'd kill you, Moss.
Playtex have changed a lot
over the last few years.
Nonetheless,
I want complete secrecy on this one,
so if anyone asks for me,
my name is Stephen Fennel.
I chose Stephen Fennel
because it's easy to remember.
Right. Except, well, you did say
Stephen Jennel earlier.
Smoke and mirrors, Roy.
Is it Fennel, is it Jennel?
If I don't know, how will they?
Who am I, Roy? I'm a ghost.
I'm a shadow. I'm gone. Pfffff!
Hello, Moss speaking.
Well done. Good presentation.
Thanks, James.
Jen, a word.
I've got Helen Buley coming in tomorrow.
Do you know who she is?
Of course I do.
She's been made head of BHDR Industries,
so obviously we need to make friends.
I know. BHDR Industries,
they're the top makers of that product
that has something to do with our company.
Exactly.
I want you up front at that meeting.
We can't have Helen going back to BHDR
saying Reynholm Industries is a boys' club.
- How does that sound?
- Oh, sounds great.
All right, see you tomorrow.
Stephen Premel.
Oh, hello. Yeah, I'm Stephen Premel.
- I think.
- You're very late. Quick.
Hello. Stephen Premel.
I'm afraid I'm very late.
Um, what exactly, um, is...?
Um... Yep...
Gavin Briers there,
with developments in North Korea.
It's five years since
the war in Iraq began.
The conflict rages on
with no hope of a solution in sight.
I'm joined by Stephen Premel,
a spokesman for the Ministry of Defence.
- Mr Premel...
- Hello. Hello.
Uh, Iraq is a gigantic
and bloody mess, isn't it?
Yes.
- Well, how do you explain it?
- Well, we shouldn't have gone to war.
- You think the invasion was a mistake?
- Oh, yes.
I'm astonished that you should
agree to this so readily
when your department
must take a lot of the blame.
What? We didn't do anything.
Well, you raised no objection
in the run-up to the war.
Yes, I did. I signed a petition.
Sorry?
I'm sorry, I'm confused.
When can I start talking about my bra?
Oh, Jen, can you bring me the prototype?
There are a couple of glitches
I need to iron out.
Sure. Guess who I'm about to meet now.
Helen Buley.
Oh, come on.
She took that football team to court for
institutional sexism, won massive damages,
and now she's head CEO at BHDR Industries.
Sorry, I kinda switched off
after the word "football".
Did you see it? Did you see it? Is he in?
Is he...? Aaah, ha-ha!
There I am,
catching up with the
news events of the day,
when who should appear
upon my television screen?
It's only the Ministry of Defence.
Oh, the news, Dragons' Den -
you're all over the schedules.
I'm sorry, Moss, but are you really sure
that you're ready to go on Dragons' Den?
- Yes. It's a brilliant product.
- Oh, no. Don't get me wrong.
You have got the science down, but it's...
well, it's all the other stuff, isn't it?
- What other stuff?
- OK, well...
OK, let's say this staple is science.
You're good at this.
What you're not so good at...
is everything else in the world.
But that's where I come in.
I can help you with all this other stuff,
you know, give you some tips
on business and presentation,
leaving you free to concentrate on this.
- What's in it for you?
- A cut.
- All right, you're in for half a percent.
- Oh!
25%.
Half a percent.
Deal.
OK, first thing we need to do is buy the
rights for the word "Abracadabra".
Agreed, but before that we've got to
sort out the overheating problem.
"Overheating problem"?
Yes, it's got a very, very serious
overheating problem.
I'll have it sorted by next week, though.
Just need to get it back off Jen.
Which has led to
significant gains in this area
and an overall yield of 22%.
Thank you very much. Jen, is it?
Yes, Miss Buley.
Please. Helen.
Uh-huh. OK, Helen.
I think as the only two women in the room we
can dispense with formalities, don't you?
Reynholm Industries has come a long way
in the past two years
if a young woman like this
can blossom within its walls.
I remember when the atmosphere here
was a lot less conducive
to what I can remember one executive
calling "working skirt".
Yes, well, I think we're all a little older
and a little wiser now, Helen.
One would hope so.
Are you OK, Jen?
My tits.
Oh! Ooh! Ohhh!
Oh, my tits are hot.
Oh! Oh, they're really, really hot.
Ohh! Oh, my tits are on fire.
Yep, my tits are on fire.
They are on fire. My tits are on fire!
Oh! Aargh!
Oh, yeah! You're right.
- 40%.
- 20%.
- 40.
- 40?
You owe me, Moss.
Helen Buley has gone away
thinking I was a stripper,
hired as a prank.
But 40%, Jen, be reasonable.
I have two black rings around here.
- I could sue you and get everything.
- All right, all right.
Good, thank you. Now we can
concentrate on your presentation.
Hey, hold on!
I'm doing presentation.
- Where'd you get pizza?
- Some idiot left it in the toilet.
I am doing presentation.
Whoa. No, hold on. Moss is my best friend,
and I'm damned if I'm gonna let ..
- Do something else.
- Like what?
I don't know. Fitness.
Fitness? People do need to be fit
to go on Dragons' Den.
Come on, Moss,
you're keeping the Dragons waiting.
- Wow.
- Hey.
- Jen, Roy.
- You look amazing.
Thank you.
You sorted out the overheating problem?
I'm completely sure that I've absolutely
sorted out the overheating problem, yes.
Unless I've made it even worse.
- How do you feel? Do you feel ready?
- My middle name is Ready.
No, that doesn't sound right.
I eat ready for breakfast.
OK, uh... maybe... maybe don't talk too
much. Let the product do the talking.
What do I do
when they want me to do the talking?
- You're scaring him.
- Oh, don't be scared, Moss.
This is one of the biggest moments
of your life coming up.
You cannot get nervous now, because if you
do, Moss, it'll be a disaster. A disaster!
- Don't! Shut up!
- I don't want to do it. I feel trapped,
like a moth in a bath.
Moss, we're already late.
Will you come on with me?
- What?
- Please.
Well, actually, maybe it's just the thing.
If Helen Buley sees it,
she'll realise I'm a proper professional,
and not a member of the sex industry.
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
You can do presentation.
And I'll do fitness.
Jen, Roy and Maurice are
IT professionals with Reynholm Industries.
They walk up the stairs
and across the room.
They nod at the Dragons.
One of them - Maurice -
puts a case on a chair.
The Dragons are beside piles of money,
with pens.
Women in the workplace...
- Take your time.
- Err...
Sorry.
Women working
in a workplace environment...
work...
in workplaces...
um... where they work.
And... as a woman,
as a worker,
as a woman worker who
works in the workplace...
Sorry, bit of asthma.
We are looking for £400,000 for 2%.
Have you got any questions?
Wow.
This music sounds like
it comes from space.
- Yeah, mate.
- It does.
Ordinary boys they ain't.
I'm having a good time. Yeah.
This is good. Good shit.
♪ Boys will be boys
♪ Boys will be boys till the end