Come on, settle!
The sooner you're settled,
the sooner this is over with.
Thank you. Now, you're going
to meet some men today
who've taken a wrong turn
in their lives.
They're going to tell you their stories,
and hopefully
make you think a little bit
about the roads you're going down.
It's not going to be any kind of fun,
so you can wipe those smiles
off your faces.
Right. Now, let's meet
our first speaker.
What the flip are you looking at?
You think this is funny?
You think this is some kind of
mother-flipping joke?
Mother-flippers think everything's
a mother-flipping joke.
Well, let me tell you
the chokey ain't no jokey, sucker.
Look at me and what do you see?
Just a badass brother
who made a mistake.
One mistake!
And now I'm staring at you gimps
every flipping day.
So what's my story?
How did a brother get here?
Well, I'll tell you.
It all started when I went
to fix a printer on floor seven.
As I recall, it was a Tuesday.
It's a... It's a lot faster now.
That's one of the advantages
of the Pentium processor.
Yeah.
I like your glasses.
I'm afraid they're not for sale.
Ha ha.
Laugh all you want,
they're not for sale.
You're funny.
Nikki! Nikki! Nikki!
What are you talking to
Clive Sinclair for?
Shut up, Rog.
Good one. Yeah, I get it.
You obviously don't, mate.
Come on! Back in your box.
Nice tie, by the way!
Thank you.
Roy, can you come here, please?
Uh, just hold on a second, Jen.
I'm giving phone support.
Okay, so how did that go? Well...
Yeah, but that's a important part
of the process.
Yes, if you don't complete that part,
there's no way that you're going
to be able to do the next bit.
Okay, so now...turn it back on again!
People...
That is rude! What is that?
Oh! Jen, I have to say "Have you tried
turning it off and on again?"
about a thousand times a day.
It's like a bloody catchphrase.
If it wasn't for you and Moss,
it would be the only thing I say.
It doesn't matter. Don't take your
bad career decisions out on the users.
I'm not saying it again today.
You know, they can just figure it out
for themselves.
You'll never go a whole day
without saying it.
- You don't think I can?
- No way.
I bet you a thousand pounds I can.
Oh! Uh-uh, that's just posturing,
a thousand pounds.
All right, okay. Hundred pounds
says I don't say it again today.
- How's that for posturing?
- All right, you're on.
- Hundred quid.
- All right.
Can you come here for a sec, please?
- Why?
- I want you to take a look at something.
Can't I do it on the phone?
Just come in! It's like 20 feet!
You all right, Moss?
I don't mind telling you, Roy,
that sometimes the people upstairs
cheese me off to such an extent
that if I were the type
to use bad language,
I'd be employing it
bitterly and repeatedly.
Whoa. Whoa, Moss, that's not like you.
Well, I'm sorry for mentioning
bad language.
No, use bad language, Moss, please!
It'll make you feel better.
Ffff...
Ploppers!
Someone told me I need a browser
on my computer.
-- Could you install one, please?
You don't have a browser
on your compu...
What is... What is that sound?
Is that coming from your laptop?
It's not supposed to sound... What the!
What's all that crap?
How long has that been... I haven't
seen that one since the '90s!
Oh, Jen, I have to fix this.
No, no, leave it.
I have it how I like it.
How you like it?
No, no, no, Jen, it's infected!
If this was a human being,
I'd shoot it in the face.
I just want you to install a browser.
That's the browser there!
Look at it! That's the browser.
Internet Explorer is a browser.
Behind the picture of the lady.
The lady's not supposed to be there!
Oh, hey, she's only there sometimes.
But what... What about the "e"?
But that's the button
for the internet, Roy.
- I don't...
-"The button for the internet"?
Jesus Christ!
Oh, shut up.
I'm not a stupid geeky-geek.
Jen, you don't need
to be a geek
to know that you need a browser
to access the internet.
Yes, you do, because as soon
as you know something like that,
it pushes out something important
and before you know it, you're painting
little figurines from Lord of the Rings.
Oh!
You know what, Jen?
Do whatever you want. I don't care.
You want to walk around with the laptop
from The Exorcist, that's just fine.
It's not my problem.
Our time is too valuable.
Come on, Moss, let's go.
It's nearly one.
Oh, don't forget, they're giving
a party for Ben Genderson at lunch.
Ben Genderson? Oh, how nice for him.
He's been here, what? A week?
When's our party?
I thought you hated parties.
I like parties.
It's balloons I don't like.
- Right.
- You don't like balloons?
Oh, don't talk to me about balloons.
- Why?
- Balloons explode, Jen.
They explode, suddenly and unexpectedly.
They are filled with the capacity
to give me a little fright
and I find that unbearable.
Where do you want to go for lunch?
It's such a lovely day.
Shall we go to the park?
Yeah, let's have a lovely lunch
in the park.
Roy, do you think if I hadn't paid
so much attention in school,
I'd be a different person?
No.
We're going to be late
for Ben Genderson's party.
So? I don't want to go to that thing.
If we go to that party,
do you know how many times
I'm going to have to say "Have you..."
The thing that I say.
Yeah, but we've got to hurry up.
We're going to be in trouble.
- I'm not running.
- Can you do a fast walk?
- No.
- I'm going to do a fast walk.
See you there.
I need to be at work.
Sorry, sir. Whole street's closed.
Suspicious package.
Come on, let's go the long way round.
We're going to miss the presentation.
We're already late.
- We're going to get in trouble.
- Calm down.
I can't, Roy.
What are we going to do?
- Moss, it doesn't matter.
- We're going to get in trouble.
You're not going to
get in trouble, Moss.
Getting in trouble is something
that happens to children.
- You're a grown man.
Hey, come here...
Why don't we bunk off?
What?
I was hoping to avoid Jen today, anyway.
Why don't we just... We'll bunk off,
we'll make a day of it,
it'll be a laugh.
Oh, my gosh! I've got to take this in.
I've never bunked off in my life.
What... What... I mean, what will we do?
Where will we go?
You know,
we'll do bunking off kind of things.
Should we really be talking
this close to the police?
I mean, it is illegal, right?
Not unless you're supposed to be
in school. Will you relax?
I'm excited, Roy. This is like
taking the blue pill in The Matrix.
I mean, bunking off,
the old me would never have done that.
Say goodbye to that guy.
That guy's history. Bang! He's gone.
Could you not say "bang"?
There's a bloody bomb somewhere.
Come on, let's just... Let's just go.
Would you stop looking so suspicious?
Which is why, after one week with us,
we honour Ben Genderson.
-- Okay, okay.
Come on, Ben, say a few words.
Well, I don't know what to, uh...
Such... Such a lovely thing to happen.
I never thought that a major corporation
would be able to focus on
one individual like this.
At my last company,
I felt rather insignificant.
So, it's, uh,
it's appreciated. It really is. Cheers.
Don't raise your glass too soon, Ben,
'cause this has all been one big ruse.
It isn't your day at all.
That's right. I thought it high time
that we give the IT department
the attention they deserve.
Where are Mark and Ray?
Oh! Um...
They're not back from lunch yet.
Really? I flew George Lucas in
to see them, as a treat.
Oh, well, Jen, more champagne for us.
Let the revels begin!
Yeah!
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
Sitting on the bus.
On the open road.
Kicking back.
Just a pair of cheeky bunkers.
- Couple of ne'er-do-wells.
- Yeah.
Roy, can I clarify something?
Are we now loitering?
Um, yeah.
'Cause it feels like travelling.
Sure, but we don't actually
want to go where this bus is going.
- So, there's an element of loitering.
- There's an aimlessness.
- Exactly.
- Yeah!
Who'd want to end up going
to where they wanted to be?
That's what the Man wants.
So true.
- Fools.
Roy. Roy, let's glare.
- What?
- Let's glare at people.
Like a couple of tough nuts.
Oh! OK. Who?
Let's glare at this sucker
on his way to work.
Yeah, feeding the corporate machine.
And, uh...
- He's coming up.
- He's getting on the bus.
Oh, no.
Why did you suggest him?
You could've suggested anybody.
What are you looking at?
We weren't.
We thought you were someone else.
What's it to you?
Don't listen to him.
We're bunking off and he's excited.
We're bunking off!
Roy has a fear of balloons.
A fear of balloons.
That's the craziest thing
I've ever bloody heard.
- Here's your wine.
- Oh, sorry, I asked for red.
- Oh, sorry.
- No, no, no, leave it.
This has been a success.
I have had a lovely, lovely time.
As thingy was saying earlier,
it's easy to go unrecognised
in a big corporation,
so it's appreciated.
It really is. Cheers.
Don't raise your glasses
too soon,
because this ruse has also been a ruse.
Ladies and gentleman,
let me introduce to you
our new head of hiring and firing,
Ben Genderson.
So, Ben, you've been circulating
throughout this fake party,
coming to conclusions.
Who's the obvious dead wood?
Well, yes. Well, it's Paul over there.
He's been putting his shopping
on expenses.
James here, he can't spell.
And, uh... Sorry, what's your name?
- Jeremy.
- Jeremy, yes. Jeremy's a drunk.
And Jen, uh, Jen lacks
basic computer skills.
Like thinking that IT stands for
Internet Things.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't really need
to know about those things.
I'm a relationship manager.
I manage my team. I'm a team leader.
And where's your team now?
I'm sorry, I'm confused.
Uh, is this my party or not?
- What are we doing?
- We are loitering.
We are shopping.
We don't have any money,
so it's definitely loitering.
Mark my words, in half an hour,
we shall be asked to leave.
Um...
- Oh, it's Jen. Yeah?
- Hello, Jen!
Where are you?
Uh, we're just, um,
we're just sort of taking a long lunch
sort of thing.
You can't take a long lunch
I've been sent an e-mail
questionnaire thing
and I have to do it today.
I don't know what
you're talking about, Jen.
It wasn't Ben Genderson's thing,
it was our thing.
And then it was some scary thing.
And now Ben Genderson's sent me
a bloody e-mail questionnaire
about my job and my computer won't work!
What do I do?
Is that the best you can do?
I'm not going to say it.
No! No, no, no, no. No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
God damn it, Roy! I didn't bunk off
so I could do some flipping perusing.
I want to taste the apple, Roy.
I want to bite the electric tiger's tail
and ride it till the end of the
mother-flipping line.
- Will you just calm down, Moss?
Oh...
- What are you doing?
- I'm shoplifting.
- You've just gone insane.
- I've never felt so alive.
You need to give this stuff back.
Okay, they're onto us. Let's just go.
And act normal.
What is wrong with you? Who are you?
I don't know any more.
What are we gonna do?
No! That's not going to work!
Okay, run! Run, run, run, run, run...
Come on! Come on!
Mmm... Mmm...
...Two two.
Hello.
Do you wish for technical assistance?
Oh, God, I hate these.
Sorry?
- What?
- How dare you
speak to me like that?
Sorry. Um, can I have
technical assistance, please?
Putting you through. Cow
- Hello.
Hello, how can I be of assistance?
- What?
- How can I be of assistance?
Um, I've got one of your laptops.
It won't get past the loading screen.
Have you tried turning it off
and on again?
Yes, look,
is there someone else I can talk to?
There is no one else available.
- All right, all right.
- Which model do you have?
What model do I have?
- Yes.
- It's a Zubion, I think.
Oh, Zubion is...
Can you press the...
I didn't get that.
Can you press...
No, that was worse, somehow.
Uh, can...
- Can?
- Yes.
Can you press...
- Can you press?
- Delete.
Delete. Can I press Delete?
Yeah. "Wheel"...
"Wheel..."
"Wheel." Eh, during.
- While, while!
- Yes, "wheel".
- Yes.
-"...shtotting... "
Hello?
All right, come on! We're nearly there.
Oh...
It's no use... I can't...
Okay, we're going down again.
-- How many times is that now?
Oh, this is ridiculous!
I don't want to do this any more!
All right... All right...
- What was all that about?
- What?
You shouldn't be messing around
on those things.
Go on.
Don't come back here.
I know your faces now!
Bunking off was a terrible idea.
I mean, you were completely
out of control.
I mean, do you even like Grand Designs?
Yeah.
You will send those DVDs
back to the shop.
Okay. I'm sorry, Roy.
It's okay. Yeah, let's just try
and get back into work
and hopefully nobody
will have noticed we were away.
Oh my gosh!
It's a robot!
I've never seen one in the wild before.
Where'd you come from, fella? Huh?
Where'd you come from?
Can we keep him, Roy?
I mean, if he doesn't belong to anyone.
I just don't understand what it's doing?
I mean, this is weird.
What is it?
- Uh, Moss?
What?
- Get away from it.
- Why?
Hello, Jen!
It's a robot!
Get away!
- What?
- Get away!
Get away from it! There's a bomb!
What are you saying?
There's a bomb in the bag!
I think this might be
a bomb-disposal robot, Roy.
I know.
We should move away from it.
Yes, we should.
But I don't seem to be able to move.
- What?
- I can't move.
- What do you mean you can't move?
- You have to move, Roy.
- I can't move.
I'm just having a couple
of problems with it.
What kind of operating system
does it use?
It's, uh..Vista.
We're going to die!
Did you try turning it
off and on again?
What?
Did you try turning it
off and on again?
What?
Have you tried turning it
off and on again?
I just won a hundred quid.
Okay. Hang on a second!
Why are you still here?
Why haven't you run away?
Oh, come on, Roy. We're a team.
I could nev... Oh, wait, I could
totally run away, couldn't I?
It's still not working!
Oh! This is a very common problem
with Vista.
I can fix this. I can fix this, Roy!
Everything's going to be okay!
Hooray!
Right. Come here, you.
Aww.
Hooray!
Wait for me!
Is there a customer support number?
Uh...
Hello, can I be of assistance?
What?
So, that's my story.
It ain't a pretty story,
but it's the only one I got.
And if you bozos don't buckle up
and fly right,
it'll be your story, too. Capiche?
What?