Jen, have a listen to this.
Moss, have you seen the newsletter?
Does this sound mysterious?
Yeah, yeah, it's quite mysterious.
I was hoping for "ruddy mysterious".
It's fairly mysterious.
I'm compiling a playlist for
a role-playing game I'm hosting.
Important to get the right atmos.
Okay, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Kind of like a Dungeons & Dragons thing.
Oh, is this something to do with sex?
Ha! Far from it, Jen.
No, you see, in role-playing,
one person is a dungeon master
or game master or keeper.
He or she controls the world and tells
the players what they're experiencing,
whether it be battling
with a coal monster
or just kicking back in a smelly
old tavern with some roguish elves.
Played over a few hours,
the game employs dice rolls
to determine the outcome
of certain events.
Now, unlike most board games
you might be familiar with,
role-playing games often use
a 20-sided dice...
- Moss?
- Yeah?
- I want to stop listening to this.
- I completely understand.
So, in the world we actually live in,
a post has opened up
for Entertainments Manager.
I could do that. That sounds great!
Better than whatever this job is.
Entertainments Manager.
It's not for you, Jen.
What are you talking about?
"Organising cultural events
for visiting business partners."
That is so me!
It's not, though.
It's really not for you.
Oh, what am I talking to you for?
Where's Roy?
Not in yet.
Is he still moping about
after that girl?
Worse than ever.
Thank God he can't play guitar.
Have you seen the pictures?
Pictures?
There's more than one of these?
Yup, there's a butt-load.
And she's Photoshopped
out of all of them?
Yeah. It's like someone
broke up with Stalin.
It's such a shame.
I've never seen him happier than he's
been the last few months. And now...
- Oh. Hi, Roy.
- Hi, Roy.
It's okay. You were obviously
talking about me.
- No, no, no...
- It's fine.
I realise I haven't been
the easiest person
to be around the last few weeks,
but I really feel like I've turned
the corner now, I really do.
So, if we could all just carry on
as normal...
My God, oh, my God...
I feel like I've come out
the other side of it now,
so everything's going to be okay
from here on...
My heart hurts!
You do seem better than yesterday.
But Roy, you've got
to snap out of this.
- I know, I know!
- Some things just don't work out.
I know you're not used to being
in a long-term relationship.
It's really rare for me!
It's so rare.
But take it from me,
most of them just don't work out.
She's right, Roy.
- And how would you know?
- I do all right.
When?
Well, if you must know,
I met a girl on holiday.
They're always on holiday,
aren't they, Moss?
Oh, shut up, Dumpo,
the elephant who got dumped!
- Hey, hey!
- Well...
No, no, it's okay. I'm... I'm all right.
I mean, I'm still a bit...
You know, she never said goodbye.
So I just kind of...
And you know, it still just hurts
just a little bit whenever I...
whenever I think about her.
So I guess all I have to do
is just never think about her!
"Simples!" Oh, she used to love that ad!
It's not for you, Jen.
What? Why not?
Entertainments Manager?
Do you know what that involves?
Well, from what I can gather,
it's just organising cultural events
for out-of-town business partners.
That's right. Yes, yes.
It's not for you.
But as far as I can see,
it won't interfere with my duties
in the IT department.
I love culture.
I've seen We Will Rock You four times!
Oh.
Well, Jen, I'd love to help you,
but traditionally,
the role of Entertainments Manager
has always been held by a man.
Mr Reynholm, I don't need
to remind you of the report
that denounced Reynholm Industries
as "an institutionally
sexist organisation"?
Now, you hold on a minute, sugar tits!
Everyone saw through that report.
And I even got that award
off those feminists.
The one shaped like
the ice cream fellow.
That's a Shithead of the Year award.
It actually says it on the base.
"Shithead of the Year."
Did you not read the base?
Oh!
- Oh, God.
- Women, eh?
What are they? Who knows?
Don't do this.
Can't live with them,
can't find them, sometimes.
What's going on in their little heads?
Don't ask me!
I'm not a flippin' women's psychiatrist.
But I have learned one or two things
from conversations with my mother.
No. No, Moss, please.
Don't go any further.
Just stop right there!
You're no good
at this kind of thing, Moss.
You'll just make it worse!
Sorry, it's just...
I've never seen you like this.
No, I know, but I'll be fine.
I will... It's just...
You can't help with this.
You just can't.
- I got it! I got the job!
- What?
Douglas gave me the job
so I'd stop talking!
Jen's Entertainments Manager.
It's not for you, Jen.
Why does everyone keep saying that?
- What happened to Jerry?
- Massive heart attack.
I'm not surprised!
Why are you not surprised?
Why is it not for me?
Jerry was, uh...
He was the company Fredo.
You're the new Fredo!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Fredo. From The Godfather
Who's Fredo again? Who's he in it?
You know, he's the brother,
whose job it is to take
out-of-town businessmen and...
Show them a good time, yeah!
That's what I have to do.
I was thinking West End show...
No, no. No, no, no, Jen.
I don't think you understand.
These men are going to expect a lot more
than a West End show.
Fredo, Jen, he was...
- He was sort of a pimp.
- Oh, shut up.
- Wasn't he, Moss?
- What?
Fredo, in the film, he was...
He was essentially a pimp.
No! He took the ring to Mordor.
Fredo was a pimp.
No. No, that film was the '70s.
Things are different now.
Businessmen are different.
Anyway. Enough about our balls!
Gentlemen, I'd like you to meet Jen.
Ah...
- Marvellous.
- Lovely.
No, no, no, no.
Jen's our new Entertainments Manager.
But she's a woman, isn't she?
Jen, I'd like you to meet
an old friend of mine, Phil,
and two men named John.
What are you up to, Reynholm?
Don't you worry, Phil.
Jen may look like an old maid
holding pennies in her arse,
but she knows the sleaziest routes round
this old town I like to call Londinius.
And I'm sure she's planned something
suitably raucous for you reprobates.
Well, yes, yes. I have tickets
for a wonderful show in the West End.
- As long as it doesn't have subtitles.
- Subtitles? No.
- Whoa! What's got subtitles?
- This thing she's bringing us to.
Subtitles? Oh, God!
I can't read while I'm also
trying to see things!
No, no, it's a show, it's a show.
There's no subtitles.
I hate subtitles.
What happened to Jerry?
His heart exploded.
Brilliant!
No, he's quite seriously ill.
That's classic Jerry!
Ah, yes.
Jerry wouldn't have brought us
to something with subtitles.
There's no subtitles, it's a show!
Come on, Jen, what type of show?
Well, uh...
Yes, well, it's very raunchy, yes.
I... I don't think
you'll be disappointed.
Women in it?
Yes, it's an all-woman show.
It's very rude.
- An all-woman show.
- And it's rude!
Eiffel Tower!
Oh, I'm so, so sorry,
I really can't apologise enough.
I've never been
so embarrassed in my life!
That woman was in EastEnders!
How dare you humiliate her?
It's not our fault you took us to
something called The Vagina Monologues,
you get there,
and it's just women talking.
That's false advertising!
Look, we're in town for five more days,
you'd better have something proper
for us to do.
And the next time you take us
to something about talking fannies,
it had better be about talking fannies!
I know you had good reasons
for giving me this award.
I should never have done that interview.
But that journalist had an agenda!
There's more.
"Women are a kind of savage animal,
"whom men have civilised
with their insatiable sexuality."
What don't you like about that?
"Women are essentially no different
from radiators."
"I like my women
like I like my toast. Hot..."
"And consumable with butter."
You don't have to remind me.
I'm all too familiar
with my misguided words.
Ladies, listen, no one could
mistake me for Gok Wan.
I have an old-fashioned mindset
but, damn it, at least I try!
And Reynholm Industries is changing,
ladies, for the better.
The glass ceiling is now a glass floor.
The women are floating above it
and the men are just looking up at them.
So what do you want from us?
What?
Oh! Please take that award back
and give it to somebody else.
Mr Reynholm, I really need
to talk to you about something.
Ah, Jen. I'd like you to meet
some very special women.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- What?
Mr Reynholm, I will not
work with prostitutes.
No, no, no. These are feminists.
You can dress it up however you like,
they still sleep with men for money.
I'm sorry, no of fence.
But I don't charge for these potatoes
and I don't like women who do.
Don't listen to her. The bitch is crazy.
Douglas wants me to see out the week.
A whole week in the company
of those idiots!
Culture's out, restaurants are out.
Oh, God, this is a nightmare!
Oh!
Men, eh?
What are they like? With their
bawdy talk and roughhousing,
and their wandering hands
and breath in the morning? Oh.
I'd like to see them have the babies!
What are you getting at, Moss?
Well, unless I'm very much mistaken,
this seems to be a problem
for which you need the male perspective.
Do you know any men?
You want a good time, right?
One that walks on the wild side
without compromising your principles?
Yeah, that's exactly what I want.
Then you got it, baby!
Which is why the game needs
a 20-sided dice.
I've not understood a word
you've just said.
What is it, some sort of computer game?
In a sense, except it uses the most
powerful processor known to man,
the human mind.
But you're not playing.
I'm not a player. But I am playing.
He sort of tells us what's happening.
I will be your guide.
Through my words, you will experience
the land of Elfenheart.
From the mighty mountains
that border the Goblin Wastelands
to the sewers that run like
a spider web through the city of Jandor.
I, gentlemen, will be your eyes.
I will be everyone you meet,
every creature you encounter,
every trap you spring.
What about him?
What's this business
with the face like a slapped arse?
I'm sorry, I just...
I just came out of a long-term
relationship so... It doesn't...
She was the greatest woman I've ever met
and I'm never going to see her again.
But it's fine, I mean,
she never said goodbye, so...
I'm not going to bore you with it.
See that you bloody don't!
I still don't understand
what this game is!
It seems gay.
Are dragons gay, Phil?
Mighty warrior priests
wielding golden staffs?
I suppose they're gay, too!
Uh...
Here are your character sheets.
John 1 , you're a unicorn man.
John 2, you're a wood fairy.
And Phil, you're the
gypsy assassin, Esmerelda.
I'm a woman?
I don't think I want to be a woman.
Just go with it. It will end.
So, gentlemen, are you prepared
to open the doors to your minds
and travel to worlds
hitherto undreamed of?
Hey, hey, hey!
Look at those funbags!
Everybody doing okay, yeah, yeah?
You good for drinks?
Loosen up! It's a role-playing party!
Jen, can I have a word?
I don't think I want to hang
with these guys.
Oh, come on, Phil.
These guys are the best.
They're gonna do things tonight
that'll blow your mind.
Really?
Look at them.
They're young, they're keen
and all they want to do
is show you a good time.
So get back there
before you hurt their feelings.
Could I...could I steal
the lovely Roy for a sec?
It's just him in all of these.
Oh, thanks, Jen, that was all
getting a little bit...
- What do you think you're doing?
- What?
Bringing everyone down
with your private life?
They don't want to know about
your miserable private life!
They're here for a good time.
Look at that face.
Who'd want to role-play with that face?
I'm sorry, Jen. I'm just...
I'm not feeling it tonight.
Then fake it, sweetheart, yeah?
You're getting good money for this.
Don't you want to get the deposit for
a flat? Leave those bad memories behind.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
I'll try harder, Jen.
Okay. Good girl.
Get back there and show
those Johns a good time.
Well, that cleaned the pipes.
I've got to thank you, Miranda,
for giving me a second chance.
Oh, don't mention it.
Although you do know I don't have the
authority to take back the award myself?
Oh, what?
No, we all make mistakes.
And you intrigue me.
Something tells me there's
more to you than meets the eye.
Do you mean the rumours
that I killed my wife?
- No. Are there rumours?
- No.
There were rumours
that there was a rumour,
but that was just bullshit.
I didn't like the way the nominations
came from inside your company.
Inside my company?
Yeah, one of the women
from the IT department
faxed a dossier of your behaviour
over the last 12 months.
One of the women in the IT department?
- Oh.
- Sorry, Phil.
"Heal all" is probably the worst spell
you could have used.
The sound of your low-level magic
attracts the attention
of the palace guards.
- Damn it!
- Oh!
One comes through the door.
- Throwing knife.
- Are you sure? Quite a low damage.
I have a plus 40% chance of a critical.
Remember the talking bunny
that gave me that magic bracelet?
Yeah, that bunny thing
gave him that thing.
You're absolutely right. Roll 'em.
Yes!
Direct hit.
The knife cleaves his head in twain
and some of his brains runneth
down John 2's invisibility cloak.
Eiffel Tower!
Oh!
- Unfortunately, he wasn't alone.
- Damn it!
- Oh!
- Ooh!
'Tis the dreaded Imperial Guard,
the cruellest of all
of Queen Elisa's troops.
At their head, someone you recognise.
"Well, well, well,
if it isn't the adventurers
"what have been causing me
all this bother."
- Lucius Santana!
-"The very same!"
Stand your men down, Lucius!
We have no quarrel with you!
"Quarrel? I just came to see
"how a mismatched bunch of
raggle-taggle adventurers
"bested some of the deadliest criminals
in Crackenwood."
- Oh!
- That's us!
"You have my thanks.
"And if ever you want to join
the Palace Guard, you know where I am."
The Palace Guard!
You have my sword.
And my staff.
And my bunny bracelet.
And whatever it is that I have.
The mist clears.
You see a lone female figure.
That's ruddy mysterious.
"Hello, Darkharden."
Hello. Who goes there?
"'Tis I, Queen Elisa Eldridge
of the Elves,
"who cruelly jilted you
not three moons ago."
Don't do this.
Just go with it, Roy.
Hello, my queen.
How are you?
"I'm fine. You look well."
So do you. Does she?
- Yes, she does, actually.
- Does she?
"So, what are you up to?"
Oh, you know, just... Just keeping busy.
Missing you a little bit.
Yourself?
"Usual boring pageantry.
"You know how the people
of Pippsiehollow love a parade."
What are you doing here?
- Sorry.
Sorry.
-- Sorry. Bear with me, bear with me.
Bear with me.
"I sense a sadness in you."
It's just hard. You know?
I miss you.
I can still smell you on our pillow.
When I close my eyes,
it's still your face I see.
It's just hard.
You were here and then you were gone.
What do you want?
"It was not easy for me
to come here, Darkharden.
"But I had one thing I felt
I needed to say to you.
- "Goodbye."
Goodbye.
Brilliant night! Brilliant!
I can't believe I've never
tried role-playing games before.
I'm going to go home and tell
the whole rugby club about it.
Roy and Moss did not disappoint.
They did not!
I'd like to see them again.
Thank you, Douglas.
That's one special little lady
you've got there.
I'm glad Jerry died.
- Eiffel Tower!
Eiffel Tower!
Before you go, Jen, I know it was you.
You broke my heart. You broke my heart.
- That's right. That's right.
- Shut up!
Oh, you've cheered up.
Oh, yeah, I'm feeling
a lot better, Jen, thanks.
Thanks to a certain Elfin queen.
What happened to Fredo, in the film?
Ah, um... Oh.
The Godfather has him killed.
I'm going to go home.
I'm not feeling too good.
Problem solved!