And every other day,
I take a short helicopter ride
to Heston Blumenthal's restaurant.
Last night, I ate a chocolate radio
that still worked in my stomach,
and a flat chicken
that was actually a glass of water.
Even the menu was edible.
They said it wasn't, but I ate it.
Sounds like you're living
the life of Riley.
Well, I actually knew Riley,
and yes, there are similarities.
And yet, there is some sadness
in your life.
Tell me about Victoria.
Well, you'll have to forgive me,
there's been quite a few Victorias.
Your wife?
Oh, my God, my wife. Oh, yes, Victoria.
What a fantastic woman.
The two weeks we were married
were unforgettable.
She disappeared in mysterious
circumstances, did she not?
She vanished while washing the car.
Despite a search
that lasted nearly five hours,
we found nothing.
So naturally, we assumed the worst.
You must miss her.
More than words could say.
I'd give anything to see her
walk through that door right now.
Hey, why don't you
take your clothes off?
- What?
- Come on, we both knew
it was on the cards
as soon as I realised you were a woman.
What if someone were to walk in?
I left strict instructions
not to be disturbed in case we had sex.
There's no way
anyone's walking through that...
Hello, Douglas.
Victoria!
But I thought you were dead!
I must say, Douglas, you still
don't seem very pleased to see me.
No, no, no, no.
I must have eaten
some bad stereo system.
- How's the wine?
- Exquisite.
From the chef's own cellar.
What are you doing, Victoria?
Last time I saw you, you were...
Washing the car?
Yes, I imagine you have many questions.
I was under a lot of stress
that day, Douglas.
I think we both were.
We both knew it wasn't working.
I picked up my sponge and bucket
with a heavy heart that day.
The rest is a blank.
The next thing I can remember
with any clarity
is being on a kayaking holiday
two years later.
That looks good. What's that?
Oh, I sort of wish I'd ordered that.
Our invisible desserts have arrived.
I know we weren't happy for that
second week of our marriage, Douglas,
but what do you say to giving us
another chance, as a couple?
I don't know.
I don't think we can just pick up
from where we left off.
No, Victoria, I'm sorry, it's over.
Oh, God.
I forgot you could do that.
Maybe we should give it another go.
Well, that is new.
How are you doing that?
That might be the dog.
Heston, I'd like to introduce you
to my wife.
I want to divorce my wife.
Why are you telling me?
Aren't you with Legal?
No.
Remind me.
IT? Relationship Manager?
Ah, well, then I probably
shouldn't have told you any of that.
Anyway, I want to divorce her right now.
Now's too late. Before now.
In fact, I want to have
already divorced her. Is that possible?
Well, as I said, I'm not a lawyer, so...
Yes, but you're a relationship manager,
and this is a relationship.
Well, um, have you told her yet?
Kind of.
I changed my FriendFace profile
from "Married" to "It's Complicated".
That's not the same as telling her,
Mr Reynholm.
Yeah, but someone will pass it on,
why not you?
- No!
- Oh, come on!
Please break up
with my vanishing car-cleaning wife,
I don't want to do it.
I don't want to do it!
I'll give you, I don't know, £10,000.
Who are you again?
I'm Jen Barber.
I'm with the IT Department
at Reynholm Industries.
Sorry, I thought
I was meeting my husband.
Mmm. Er, Mr Reynholm asked me
to convey a, um, a message to you.
Um...
Mrs Reynholm, how long have you
and Mr Reynholm known each other?
- About 10 years.
- Ten years.
Ten wonderful years.
Who are you?
Mrs Reynholm... Can I call you Victoria?
- No.
- Mrs Reynholm,
sometimes there is a day
and then there is a night.
Sometimes, there is a morn.
And then there is an eve, flowers grow,
trees are cut down.
Babies are born but, um, lawyers exist.
What are you trying to say?
Oh, I can't do it, I just can't.
Let me guess.
My husband wants to leave me
and he paid you a large amount of money
so that you would spare him
the embarrassment of facing me.
Yes, but I'm not going to
take the money. I feel sick.
Of course you do.
You're a normal person.
- You're not upset?
- No, because I'm not a normal person.
You see, what you're trying to do here
but can't,
if the tables were turned,
I wouldn't find it difficult at all.
In fact, it's how I met his first wife.
Oh, I didn't know
these were edible, too.
They're not.
What's all that?
I have to spend the afternoon
with Douglas.
Somehow I've been drafted
into his legal eagle fantasy.
Have you ever spent
any serious time with that man?
He's unbelievable.
You should hear the way
he talks about women.
Oh, yeah, he's some piece of work.
He's like a sexy Hitler.
I mean, I don't expect
to be put on a peddle stool,
but please, just show a little respect.
Uh, I'm sorry.
You don't expect to be put on a what?
On a, on a peddle stool.
A peddle stool?
What's a peddle stool?
Oh, you know, you put women on it
when you admire them,
you know, the phrase.
Oh, yeah, no, the famous phrase
"to be put on a peddle stool".
Pedestal!
- What?
-"Pedestal" is the word!
What's a peddle stool?
Did you really think there was
such a thing as a peddle stool?
Shut up, everyone has blind spots.
Uh, can you, uh, come and help me
sort through all this legal crap,
please, Moss?
I'd rather not, I've not had
good experiences with the legal system.
How come?
Well, when I was 11 , I broke
the patio window and my mother sued me.
She sued you?
Yeah, um, to teach me a lesson.
She's always been
a very aggressive litigator.
Can you even do that?
Can you sue your children?
It was kind of a show trial
in the kitchen.
She made a little gallery for the cats.
Aw.
What happened?
She won.
I'm still paying costs.
Peddle stool.
212 million quid? You can't be serious!
Oh, we're quite serious, Mr Reynholm.
But that's enough to bring
Reynholm Industries to its knees.
Bloody blast! This is up my arse!
That is the amount.
It is not up for negotiation.
Balls from hell, you shit twins.
Calm down, Mr Reynholm.
Bollocks to be telling me to calm down,
my old chap.
She wants 220 titty million quid
and you tell me to calm down?
- You're fired.
- I'm not your lawyer.
Piss off!
I'm going to represent myself.
I'm not your lawyer.
You sit there, all confident.
Yeah? But when this goes to court,
that's when the talking stops.
Mr Reynholm.
Uh, there might actually be
more talking in court.
This would actually be
a comparatively small amount
of talking, what we're doing here.
- Oh, I see.
- Sorry.
No, no, that's all right.
It's what I pay you for.
Look at her, cold as ice.
But I tell you this.
Behind those shades, she's terrified.
One thing you should know
about me, Jen,
when I put my mind to something,
it gets done.
Representing myself
is the kind of challenge I relish.
Well, you'll have to do
a lot of preparation.
Bring it on.
Uh, what's this?
It's my suit. I made it myself.
Took me a few days.
Um, how did you find time
to prepare for the trial?
How did I what?
Mrs Reynholm, you say
that in the short time you were married,
you became indispensable to Mr Reynholm.
In what way were you indispensable?
I had to brush his teeth.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Well, that's not an expression?
- No.
You got the brush.
You applied toothpaste to it.
You moved it into his mouth.
You moved your hand up and down.
Well, if I didn't do it,
he wouldn't do it.
Make a note. "Brush teeth."
Now, you're asking
for quite a large amount.
I think it is an appropriate amount.
Bollocks.
Mr Reynholm.
Yes, Your Honour?
I would ask you to refrain from using
that kind of language in my courtroom.
And which word in particular
do you object to, Your Honour?
You only said one.
- Could you read it back?
- Mmm...
-"Bollocks."
- Don't read it back!
Why do you say
it is an appropriate amount?
Mr Reynholm caused me great distress.
I feel I'm entitled to some restitution.
Besides, it's not as if he ever put
the money to good use,
as the film proves.
Your Honour, may I present
the central exhibit to our case?
It is, I'm afraid, a sex tape.
A sex tape?
Which one?
The alien craft
appears to have dropped its shields.
Thank you, Female Chekov.
Female Sulu, beam their captain aboard.
But Captain, are you sure?
But she's hurt. She may need our help.
Jim,
even if she's injured as you say,
I can't do an examination on a new
species without proper research.
Damn it, Jim!
I'm a sexy doctor, not a sexy scientist.
Female Sulu, you have your orders.
Perhaps the good doctor thinks
that certain alien species
- do not fall under the Hippocratic Oath.
I have never refused treatment
to a patient, Female Spock,
and you know that.
- I think we've seen enough.
- Your Honour, I object.
There's a brilliant bit coming up.
Mr Reynholm. Are you ready to start
your cross-examination of Mrs Reynholm?
I am, Your Honour.
But rest assured,
it will be a normal examination.
I am not in any way cross.
You are Victoria Reynholm, are you not?
Mr Reynholm,
we have already established that.
Might I suggest you try
less to do an impression
of a lawyer you once saw
on the television
and make your case
as simply as you possibly can?
Wise words, my learned lord.
Victoria, you've spoken about
the real me,
and I think it's time we heard
a little about the real you.
Isn't it true that you used to be a man?
No.
It isn't true, you say?
It is untrue.
Who am I thinking of?
I think you mean April,
the woman you had a fight with.
No further questions, my lord.
What? Your entire case rested on that?
- Yes, Your Honour.
- No. Wait, Mr Reynholm.
You can't leave it at that.
Uh, You Honour, may I confer
with my relationship manager?
- What's up, Jen?
- Um,
you've got to request more time
to prepare a proper defence.
Your Grace, may I approach the bench?
Have you brushed your teeth?
- No.
- Then you may not.
Your Grace,
I need to prepare a proper defence.
The one I just did there was rubbish.
Yes. He's some piece of work.
Aye. We're all very happy
at Reynholm Industries.
- Are you telling the truth?
- Yes.
Then why are you so ill at ease?
Well...
If you must know,
I was in a court myself, recently.
This very courtroom, in fact,
where I gave testimony
against a former soldier who...
I was having a massage and he kissed me
on my bottom, Your Honour.
I see.
I'm sure you can understand
my discomfort.
Are you all right? Can you continue?
I can continue, thank you.
The way you tell it, your employer
sounds like a paragon of virtue.
That's right.
And furthermore,
I would like to say at this point
that I think this whole case
to be a damp squid.
Thank you. No further questions.
Ooh, I have one more
question, Your Honour.
- Yes?
- Uh, what did you say?
- What?
- What did you say the case was?
May I have it read back, please?
"I believe this entire case
to be a bit of a damp squid."
A damp squid?
What does that mean?
Oh, no, Jen. It's, um...
It's an expression.
Uh, it means that I believe
that everything
that's been said in this case
-everyone already knew.
- Mmm, yes.
But did you say "damp squid"?
- That's right.
- Did you not mean "damp squib"?
No. It's "squid".
What's a squib?
It's not "squid".
Squids are already damp.
Hence the phrase.
Your Honour, please.
It is "squib".
I must say, I find it extraordinary
that you, a man in your early thirties,
could have reached
this point in your life
without knowing that it is "squib".
- I think it's "squid".
- I have no further questions.
- No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
- That will be all.
- Everyone has a blind spot.
- I said, that will be all!
Your name is Maurice Moss, is it not?
Sorry.
Bit nervous, so, yeah.
It's fizzy. It's very fizzy.
It's fizzy, it's gone fizzy.
-- Ow! Come on!
That's electric.
It's electric in there.
It's, uh...
Got a shock.
Your name is Maurice Moss, is it not?
It is not.
Sorry, yeah. Sorry, um...
My mother sued me.
Just, um, relax. Take your time.
Try to answer the questions
as clearly as you can.
Thank you, my love.
Your name is Maurice Moss, is it not?
Chair. It's...just the chair's faulty.
No further questions, my lord.
Don't you have anything?
She's going to take you
to the cleaners, Mr Reynholm.
Yep. I suppose she will.
What's that?
Oh, God. I think I may
have found our miracle.
Can you state your full name, please?
Richmond Felicity Avenor.
And you worked at
Reynholm Industries for a time.
I did. For over four years.
- And what did you do?
- I don't know.
Why did you leave?
Well, my life wasn't really
going anywhere.
I was part of the whole
Goth/death metal subculture.
But it wasn't making me happy.
It was all a bit gloomy.
It's round about that point
that I developed scurvy.
Ooh. Now, that sounds unpleasant.
On the contrary.
Catching scurvy was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Made me take
a long, hard look in the mirror.
And I didn't like what I saw,
I can tell you that.
Not just because
my teeth had fallen out.
Which is why I founded
"From Goth 2 Boss".
Is it okay if I play a DVD?
Does it have anything whatsoever
to do with this case?
Not really, Your Honour.
Then you may proceed.
Where are you going? Is it to the top?
If not, why not?
Go to the bloody top.
Is it because you're a Goth?
Did you know that Goths
have some of the lowest
life satisfaction levels
of any subculture,
with the exception of traffic wardens?
That's why you don't see
any Goth traffic wardens.
That would be a deadly combination.
We at "Goth 2 Boss" work with Goths
at various locations around the UK
to bring out their hidden potential,
By encouraging them to engage in
- everyday healthy pursuits.
- Everyday healthy pursuits.
- Such as sports.
- Mixing with other humans.
- Yay!
- Extended laughter sessions.
Introducing colour to your wardrobe.
Just look at these results.
This is Debbie.
She used to hang around railway stations
with her hands in her sleeves.
Now she's a lifeguard in Mumbai.
"From Goth 2 Boss. "
You know it makes sense.
Unless you're not a Goth,
in which case...
"From Goth 2 Boss"
remember the name.
But what does this have to do with
my divorce proceedings, my kind fellow?
Well, Mr Reynholm,
I'm here to tell you that that woman
is not Victoria Reynholm.
Her name is Melanie Crawford,
a former "From Goth 2 Boss"
pupil of mine.
Sing, you canary.
Well, during our sessions,
she seemed more interested in you
than getting any better.
I don't think she ever truly
exorcised the Goth within.
Scratch away that fake tan
and beneath you'll find
the purest white foundation.
Yeah, that was more
of a phrase than anything.
Oh, actually, um...
No, sorry. That's not her.
Oh, sorry about that.
Um, that's not her.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
you've heard a few things
over the past few days,
none of which cast me in
a particularly favourable light.
Stories
of expensive sex tapes.
Rumours of me killing my first wife.
No, no one's mentioned that.
But you know,
there's one thing I do want to say.
Just one thing...that I...
Mr Reynholm?
Mr Reynholm, please.
Mr Reynholm, this really is
the most pathetic display
I think I've ever seen.
May I say something, Your Honour?
Why not?
Lying here,
pretending to have a heart attack,
you see a desperate man.
Not pretending!
A man who has exhausted all of his time,
all of his resources,
on an expensive trial
that has resulted in...
humiliation.
But think not of him.
Think of the employees
of Reynholm Industries.
Think of the man
who was sued by his mother,
the simpleton who thought the phrase
"damp squid" was correct.
These are the people I want you to
consider when making your judgment.
For Reynholm is not just the name
of this ridiculous man
who keeps opening his eyes
whenever he thinks no one's looking,
Reynholm is the name of the family
his employees have found in each other.
We are all Reynholms.
Hurt him
-and you hurt...
- Oh, all right, then,
-we'll take 70 million.
- Hooray!
- Mmm.
I'm getting oak.
- Right.
Cheers!