- Have you nearly finished, Roy?
- Yep.
- You're taking a very long time.
- It's a very complicated problem.
You've got a lot of... chabaranks
in your hard drive. I'll get them out eventually.
Urh! Frustrating!
Come on, work!
Work, you bloody computer!
- Nadine, do you know about digital cameras?
- Oh, Roy might.
I do, as it happens.
I'm an amateur photographer, actually.
I just got this new one,
but it's really complicated.
That's fixed.
- What was wrong with it?
- Wasn't turned on.
Oh...
I don't even know why I got rid
of my old one - it was working fine.
Well, these all look good.
What's going on with this fella?!
Look at him! He's pulling a mad face!
He looks completely mental.
That's Dave, my brother.
He's got a very serious condition.
When I said "mental" there,
I meant mental in the sense of... intelligent.
You know, like he's a big reader.
- He has boss-eyedness.
- Bossiednis?
He's permanently boss-eyed.
That must be a big pain in the arse.
It is. And the terrible thing is, people think
there's actually something funny about this.
No! Who could think
there's something funny about this?
But it's a proper condition
and he really suffers, he really...
Oh, hey...
I'd just give anything
if Dave could have a normal life.
- Oh, hey now...
- Kimberly, are you OK?
It's just... Dave.
Oh, poor Dave.
Hey, I've got a great idea.
Why don't we do something
to raise money for people like Dave?
You know, like... We must be able
to think of something... Like a fun run!
- That's a good idea.
- Or a nude calendar.
Yes!
I would say that's maybe even a better idea
than the fun-run idea.
We could call it "The girls of the 7th floor".
Yes!
- It's a very strong theme.
- Roy could be the photographer!
I could do the photographs. Because
I said I was an amateur photographer.
Let's do a brainstorm.
I'd like to be November, if that's OK.
- Can I be April?
- Yes.
In October we've got to have
a Halloween theme...
Boss-eyedness is something
which affects 1% of Britons.
It doesn't impair eyesight, yet people with
boss-eye are routinely discriminated against.
Just like any. form of discrimination,
it should be stopped
But we can only do so with your help.
That's right - we're looking at you.
It's not funny, Jen.
- It's a very serious condition.
- I know it is. I know it is. I'm sorry.
Look, this is exactly the kind of discrimination
we are fighting against.
- And what do you need from me?
- I just need a little time off work.
We're trying to raise money
for the boss-eyed.
- Who? Who is?
- Just me and some people.
Oh, yeah? Who?
People from upstairs.
You wouldn't know them.
- Oh, OK. What are you gonna do?
- Well...
- Hi.
- Hiya.
- What are you talking about?
Er, nothing. I'm just talking to Jen
about a private project.
What is it?
It's just a private project I'm doing
that's private.
What is it?
It's just a thing. It's just a big bloody
pain-in-the-arse thing that I might do.
Oh, you are being modest.
It's a very kind thing you're doing,
very generous, very charitable.
I really am impressed.
Good for you.
What's he done, persuaded all the girls
on seven to do a nude calendar for charity?!
- Bye.
- Bye, Moss.
- Oh, God, he's right.
- Oh, no... How the hell... No, no... Aww!
- He made it sound sleazy!
- It is sleazy!
Oh, what kind of man
would want to photograph
a bunch of beautiful women
without any clothes on, Roy?
The kind of man
who wants to help people, Jen!
- No, I don't like it. I find it very offensive.
- No, it's going to be tasteful.
No, it's not.
You're right, it's not. It's not.
It's going to be rude. It's going to be sexy.
All the things men like.
And it'll make a million quid for that charity.
- No, no, no, no. Absolutely not.
- Why not?
Taking your clothes off... If it's unemployed
men or old ladies from Yorkshire, it's fun.
If it's sexy women, it's oppression.
No, I will not give you any time off for this.
Well, OK. Then I will do it in my own time.
- Roy, you're behaving like a horny teenager.
- No, you are.
- For God's sake, try and have some dignity.
- No, I won't. I won't.
- Sit down.
- No.
- Try and have an adult conversation.
- I'm doing it. It's for charity.
And there's nothing you can do about it!
You're embarrassing yourself!
Roy, stop it! Come back here!
Roy, don't be silly, come back!
Roy!
- I'm really pleased we've had this talk.
- Thanks for seeing us.
- Any advice you need about anything...
- Oh, you're so lovely.
Hiya.
Roy, thank God you're here. Jen's been telling
us how the calendar would've been sexist...
Oh, has she?
How it'd be much better
if we used old ladies or unemployed men.
Ohhh, good.
She thinks we'll make a lot more money
because of the "ah" factor.
The "ah" factor?
The thing that makes you go, "Ah"
when you hear about it.
Oh, yeah...
But will anyone actually want to see old
women or destitute men with no clothes on?
Won't that just make people go, "Agh!",
rather than "Ah"?
Guys, I've got a great idea. Why don't we
all ask our grans to do the calendar?
- Aaarrghh!
- That is a great idea!
Oh, Nadine, you are so full of ideas.
But can I... Hold on one second.
What's our theme? Isn't our theme "Girls of
the 7th floor"? That was a very strong theme.
Yes, Roy, but now the theme
can be "Grans of the girls of the 7th floor".
Oh, yeah...
I don't want to take photos of grannies.
This could do very well, Roy. This could be
tasteful. Like the one Helen Mirren did.
Old ladies, pot plants covering their bits -
you know the sort of thing.
An erotic calendar
the whole family could enjoy.
Roy, you can't drop out now.
Douglas has paid for the studio time.
- What? Has he?
- Yeah. He's very interested in this project.
And I just have to say how I'm finding
this whole thing just... so moving,
how so many men have shown interest
and support for the calendar.
I mean, people really do care
about the boss-eyeds.
Roy... you can't drop out now.
I wasn't... wrong about you, was I, Roy?
I thought you were special.
I am.
I'm so special. I... No... I...
Let's do it!
Let's go round up those grans!
Thank you! Oh, thank you!
That's OK.
- Hi.
- Hi!
You know,
we could just get a proper photographer.
- Oh, no, I'm happy to do it.
- OK.
- How's it going?
- Not a great start, I have to say.
Of all the girls on seven,
only nine have grans that are still alive.
Of that nine, one is having a...
hip replacement on the day of the shoot,
one is a little... senile
and may not know what's happening...
and the last one...
the last one has a gangrenous arm.
But she still wants to do it.
So all I have to do now is hit the streets
and find six old women that I've never met
who'd be happy to take all their clothes off
and let me take photographs of them.
Why are you doing this?
Same reason I do everything, Jen -
to have sex with a lady.
Ah...
What?
I said,
"Do you want to be in a nude calendar?"
- Do I want a calendar?
- No, no. No.
Do you... want...
to do...
a nude calendar?
- For charity.
- Oh, for charity!
Oh, well, in that case, yes, I'll take it.
How much is it?
No, no, no. No, no. No.
Do you want to do a calendar?
But the doctor's already changed my catheter.
No, no... No.
I need you... to take all your clothes off...
and have me take photographs of you.
Oh, you remembered your old mum's birthday.
IT?
Jen, hi.
I just wanted you to know
if this calendar doesn't make a million,
I'm holding you responsible.
What?! That's not very fair.
I'm sad to say that the only secure route
to a knighthood in this sorry age
is via charity work.
You can't do that. It wasn't my idea.
Nonetheless.
The idea came from your department,
and as head of the department
it's your nuts on the block.
- Oh, Mr Reynholm...
- Don't worry, Jen.
Just make it as sexy as hell
and watch the money pour in.
Sexy, sexy, sexy.
Every page sexier than the last.
Mr Reynholm...
Oh, grans... Grans aren't sexy.
That's not gonna make any money.
What kind of society are we living in?!
- What?
- Apparently we live in the kind of society
that sees a man who just wants
to take naked photos of some old ladies
as some sort of weirdo!
Who deserves to be chased and shouted at
and beaten... and chased...
- Did you tell them it's for the boss-eyeds?
- Oh, I did, I did.
I did tell them that, Jen, and you know what?
They just laughed at me.
What?
They just laughed at me, Jen.
They don't care about the boss-eyeds.
Wait, Roy. You know what? Maybe
we should rethink the theme a little bit.
"Grans of the girls of the 7th floor" -
it's such a mouthful.
Why don't we just bring it back
to "Girls of the 7th floor"?
- You said it was sexist.
- Oh, ppfftt! It's empowering!
- Sexist! How dare you be so patronising?
- Oh, you... Whoa-whoa-whoa...
And you'd enjoy it, Roy. Yeah, you'd love
to take those photos, wouldn't you?
You'd enjoy taking those photos.
I bet you would. You'd enjoy that a lot more.
D'you know what I'm talking about?
Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh?
- I don't know.
- Oh, come on!
No, no. I don't think Kimberly would like it.
And I don't want to make any wrong moves.
I cannot blow this one.
Kimberly is the best thing that ever happened
to me, and she hasn't happened to me yet.
We are not gonna make any money
with grannies.
I'm back!
- What? What do you mean?
- I'm back. From holiday.
- You were on holiday?
- Yes, I was on holiday.
- Oh, that's right...
- Yes, yes, yes...
- You didn't know I was on holiday?
- No, no, no, we did. Where did you go?
You didn't know I was on holiday!
Oh, we did, we did... We missed you.
I've been gone a week!
- A week?!
- Wow!
- Hm...
- What?
- You know what's very in at the moment?
- I don't.
Geeks. You lot.
The whole nerd thing.
Geek chic. It's very in.
So?
So it's a calendar
that celebrates scientific achievement?
- That's right.
- About time!
Think of it as an opportunity
to re-enact all of your favourite moments
from the history of science.
And maths?
- And maths.
- Yes!
Oh, I'm sorry. Excuse me.
- Yep?
- OK, are they all there?
- Yep.
- You rounded up your best-looking friends?
Yep.
OK, great, Roy. Remember, it's gotta be sexy.
Sexy, sexy, sexy.
Yep.
OK, so...
if the rest of you want to take lunch...
I'll do Moss first.
Laters.
So I'll hold up the beaker
like, "Ah! I've discovered something."
- Exactly. Yes.
- But what have I discovered?
- It doesn't matter.
- I think it does a bit, actually.
Um, OK, you have discovered... nuclear bombs.
In a beaker?
You're right. It's surprising.
So give me "surprised".
Yeah! That's it.
And it's confusing.
Yes. You're "confused".
And you are afraid of the consequences...
Give me fear! Fear!
Yeah. That's good. That's good.
OK, nice, nice.
And... if... if you're hot or anything, Moss,
maybe you could undo
some buttons on your shirt.
No, I'm all right, thanks, Roy.
Maybe just undo your top button.
Why?
It's hot. It's a hot lab.
Because of all the... fusion.
- Fission!
- Fission. Yeah.
That's it.
Maybe just one more button.
OK. That's good.
And maybe you could, er...
maybe you could get down on all fours.
Why?
Because you had some microscopic
nuclear things and you dropped them.
- Oh, did I? Oh...
- Big klutz!
- Oh, nightmare! Oh...
- They're down there somewhere.
- It's a pain. Oh, where are they?
- Yeah... And you're getting angry.
- Well, I would. It's frustrating.
- Because you can't find them.
- Arhhh...
- Arrhh! Grrr!
You know how you growl
if you can't find stuff.
- Grrr!
- That's it.
And there are other people in the lab
and they're being so noisy.
OK. Shh!
- That's it.
- Shh!
- Bit less of...
- Yes.
And... and then it occurs to you
that maybe you put your microscopic
nuclear things in your back pocket.
Oh, did I? Oh...
That's a pain. Why would they be there?
And yet I've put them there.
- Yeah.
- It's strange.
Yeah...
- You're working hard. You're tired.
- Well, I've been busy.
- Oh, they're being noisy again. Shush them.
- Shh! Shh! Shh!
- That's good, Moss. Yeah...
- Shh!
OK, so just give me a cheeky
sort of "I've been a naughty boy" look.
But I've just solved Fermat's Theorem.
Yes, but... you solved it in a way
that the stuffed shirts of the time
would've found very naughty.
Am I Fermat?
Because if I am, these clothes are wrong.
Yeah... You're more...
You're a naughty mathematician.
Roy, you're doing it wrong.
The lighting is all wrong.
The pictures are gonna be very gloomy, Roy.
This whole set-up is inadequate.
It's a celebration.
You've just discovered penicillin.
But why are our tops off?
I always take my top off when I'm celebrating.
Don't you?
Oh, yeah, I suppose so. Yeah, of course.
OK... Cavort!
That's it.
Yeah!
Thank God for all that penicillin.
Touch each other in a celebratory way.
Yeah! That's it.
Yeah... Yes...
That's good.
That's it. Ruffle your hair.
That's good. OK. Nice, nice.
That's it. Look over like that...
You... pick him up, like a wheelbarrow,
and you walk with him,
and then you come in this way. OK?
Like any. form of discrimination,
it should be stopped
But we can only do so with your help.
That's right - we're looking atyou.
Thank you.
I just wanted to say a few words.
Hey, come on. We did it.
This is exciting, isn't it? Reynholm Industries'
first sexy new charity calendar.
Come on, goofy! We wanna see the calendar!
I can't wait. I hereby announce that
speech over and the calendar ready to go.
And I think I speak for all men here
when I say I can't wait to get that box open
and feast my eyes upon its sexy contents!
Whoa! Someone's played an awful prank.
There's nothing here
but gloomy pictures of morons.
No, not morons. Geeks.
They're sexy now - you know, geek chic.
Geek chic? I wanna tear my eyes out!
This is horrible! Horrible!
- This is your fault.
- It was Roy's idea.
You idiot! I wouldn't buy this
and it's in aid of me!
- I didn't do it.
- I'm talking to her!
It's hard to tell with your mad eyes.
- Sorry we're late.
- Oh, here are the calendars! Brilliant!
Oh, great! We're on a calendar.
Box-fresh!
There goes the entire audience
for our calendar.
And they got it for free.
Roy, I don't care
that no one liked the calendar.
That was... the nicest thing
that anyone's ever done for me.
- Really?
- Really.
The doctor's already changed my catheter.
Roy? What's wrong?
Uh... Nothing.
Er, no, I...
Don't let me stop the kissing. Let's...
Shhh...
Nnah!
- Oh, no...
- Roy, are you OK?
Mm. I'm just tired.
Let's... Oh...
Cavort!
- You're doing it wrong.
- Cavort!
- The doctor's already changed my catheter.
Aaarrrhh!
Roy, what is it?
Kimberly...
it's not gonna work out.
Aww...