I'm sorry, guys. I wish I could have
come here with better news.
But according to these projections,
Reynholm Industries
is in a critical position.
We took a major downturn last year.
Like the rest of the economy.
And as a result,
we have estimated losses
at well over 400 million pounds.
Before we go on, Linda,
do you need to go to the toilet?
No.
Then why are you doing a wee-wee walk?
It's incredibly odd and distracting.
Maybe it's just me.
No, no, it's not just you, Douglas.
I'm also finding it very distracting.
- Sorry, Linda.
- Don't worry about it, Jen.
It is not a wee-wee walk.
I am actually doing a round-the-world
virtual triathlon for charity,
using an iPhone application
and Google maps.
Look, I'm in Spain.
God, that's hugely impressive.
- Haven't you just had a baby?
- So they tell me.
Oh, for God's sake.
Sorry,
did that sound like words?
No, do go on. And congratulations
on getting an iPhone.
I say we get in Silvio Bernatelli.
Bernatelli? The most successful
businessman of the year?
Why, a word from him
can make or break a business.
Look, Reynholm Industries
is in a tough spot.
But with Bernatelli as an investor,
I think we can come out on top.
This is very convincing, Linda.
Damn good job.
Damn good, bloody good, damn good job.
You're the best woman here.
You are an excellent woman.
Linda, bloody Linda.
"I'm so good at business things.
Reynholm Industries."
God, do you have any idea
how annoying this woman is?
I have an inkling.
Ohh! I just had a eureka moment.
Why do I keep my phone
in my trouser pocket?
It's too far,
but look at this, top pocket.
Yeah? Not as far. Yeah?
Yeah? Look at that.
See how smooth that is?
Ooh, mama!
Do you see that?
Do you wish you saw that?
- Sorry, did I interrupt?
- No.
She had a baby like yesterday
and she's already invading Spain.
-- Linda just had a baby?
Wow, well, you'd never know.
-- What?
- Too much information.
- What, that she had a baby?
- Come on.
- Moss, it's a natural part of life.
It's not a natural part of my life
and I aim to keep it that way.
You should be okay.
Oh, what's that jacket for?
It's not for anything.
It was a present. Julia got it for me.
Oh, how is Julia the orphan?
- Don't call her that.
- Why?
That's the first thing
you told us about her.
I totally think of her
as Julia the orphan.
Yeah, well, get out of the habit of it.
What if it slips out
when you meet her in person?
I'm hardly likely to say,
"Hello, Julia the orphan" to her, am I?
I totally would say that to her.
- Yeah, I know you would.
- But she's still an orphan, right?
Yes. Her parents haven't
come back to life.
Have you found out the story yet
what happened to them?
No, she doesn't really like
talking about it.
Are you not super curious?
Oh, I would be.
Yeah, you know, it's...
- It's none of my business.
- Maybe they're not really dead.
Maybe she doesn't know
what the word "orphan" means.
Maybe she thinks it just means...
house proud.
I'm leaving now.
- Um, Roy...
- Yeah?
What's that jacket for?
It's not for anything.
Will you be wearing that
all the time now?
Yeah, maybe.
Julia thinks I can pull it off.
- You don't like it?
- It's the worst thing ever!
You look like a tall girl.
Maybe a little feminine.
Ah, well, I can understand
why you wouldn't like it, then.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Oh, come on, this Linda business?
We get this six or seven times a week,
it's always the same,
it's never about a man.
You're just one of those women.
You're one of those women
who don't like women.
Burn it.
You should burn the jacket.
- And all this for Sports Relief?
- We all have to do our bit.
First you made me want
to go to the toilet,
and now you make me
want to be a better person.
Bit of news on the Bernatelli front,
by the way, Douglas.
His translator is sick,
so we'll have to hire one.
I could translate if you want.
Can you speak Italian, Jen?
Very impressive.
Not before I've flushed the toilet,
thank you very much.
- Beautiful and delicate young lady.
- With such butch hands.
- Oh!
I'm kidding, I'm kidding,
you've got lovely hands.
And that's a lovely ring.
I don't think I've noticed that before.
It was my mum's.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry, Julia.
I didn't mean to...
I know you don't like
talking about all that stuff.
- No, I'm sorry, Roy.
- Yeah?
I should just tell you the whole story
because you're going to have to know
sooner or later.
Mmm-hmm.
If you don't mind,
- I'd like to get it all out now.
- Okay. Sure.
Just as long as we never
talk about it again.
Yeah.
There was a fire.
A fire? Oh, God, that's awful!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
We were on holiday.
We went to a Sea Parks.
- You know, Sea Parks like SeaWorld.
- Yeah, sure, Sea Parks.
- It was during a sea lion show.
- Oh...
A fire...
...during a sea lion show...
...at Sea Parks?
The flames surrounded us so quickly
and we couldn't... We couldn't...
- Oh, are you okay?
- I'm okay, I'm okay.
Just, just promise me
we'll never talk about it again.
Sure. Of course, of course.
- But how did the...
- I don't want to talk about it!
You don't speak Italian?
No.
Why did you say you did?
No one was paying any attention to me.
So, what did you actually say
at the meeting?
I don't know.
Very impressive.
He wants me to do
a conference call with him.
- What am I going to do?
- All these lies, Jen.
This is exactly what happened
with the Iraq War.
It's not that much of a lie, Moss,
because I have always wanted
to speak Italian and I can sound
like I'm speaking Italian,
so it's more or less the same thing.
Yeah, except to Italians
or people who can understand Italian.
Exactly. Oh, God!
I'm just going to blue-sky this.
Would it be of any help whatsoever
if I were to install a voice-activated
translation programme on your laptop?
No, stupid idea, stupid idea.
No, no, no, no. Voice activate...
Does that mean someone would speak
and a translation would appear
on a computer screen?
Actually, now that you put it like that,
that could work.
Well done. Good idea, Jen.
Thank you?
The jacket!
He's still wearing the jacket!
You all right, Roy?
Is it the jacket?
Because it should be.
- No, it's, um...
- What?
Julia told me the story.
- So, what happened?
- Her parents died in a fire.
- Oh, God, I'm sorry, that's horrible.
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah, it was a fire.
At Sea Parks.
- Sea Parks?
- Yeah.
- With the...
- With the whales and everything, yeah.
Oh, okay.
- Sea Parks?
- Yeah.
- Huh.
- A fire?
- That's right.
At the sea lion show, apparently.
Aren't those shows
usually out in the open?
Well, yeah. Yeah, I mean,
that's what I would've...
- Yeah.
- Lots of water everywhere.
Yeah, I mean, I would imagine
the whales need a lot of water.
I don't think you can have
whales in a place
where there isn't a huge amount
of water.
It just seems like a weird place
to go on fire.
It's a very weird place to go on fire!
A fire at a Sea Parks?
It's the weirdest thing I've ever heard!
I mean, maybe...
Maybe if there were plastic seats,
maybe they could go on...
They don't have plastic seats
at Sea Parks.
How do you know?
Roy, when I was on holiday,
I lived at Sea Parks.
It's the funnest, wettest,
most splish-splashy place in the world.
Okay, did you go
and see the sea lion show?
Three times a day for two weeks.
- And did they have plastic...
- No, it's all stone steps.
Then what went on fire?
I've checked Wikipedia. There is no
mention of a fire at any Sea Parks.
Do you think maybe she's lying?
No. I mean, why would she lie?
And if she was going to lie,
why would she use this one?
A fire at a Sea Parks?
It's wrecking my head!
I mean, if she had said
that her parents had drowned,
I'd be the happiest man in the world.
But a fire? At a Sea Parks?
I mean, it's just... It just...
Oh, it's just...
It opens up a lot of questions.
- Well, maybe you could ask her.
- No, no, no, no.
We can never talk about it again.
- Well, maybe you could just...
- No, no. No, no, no.
We can never talk about it
for the rest of our lives.
Well, then I suppose
you're just going to have to
try and stop thinking about it.
That's another great idea!
You're on fire!
If you'll pardon the expression.
I would be very happy
to come and have a look.
Uh, next week is good for me.
We're certainly looking forward
to your visit
and can't wait to give you
the full Reynholm Industries experience.
He says he's looking forward
to meeting me.
Oh! Okay.
Ciao.
Maybe you're the best woman.
12 exits!
There are 12 exits!
- What are you doing?
- Ooh. What?
What are you doing on the computer?
Masturbating.
Badoo!
Isn't it Bernatelli today?
Shouldn't you be preparing?
No, I think I'm okay, Moss.
I've learnt a few conversational basics
and when he gets going,
I'll just fire up this baby.
I do want to feel refreshed, though
for the meeting,
so I'm going to go to sleep
for a few hours.
Is that what you're having for lunch?
A big pile of mashed potato?
I fancied it.
It's the Sea Parks, isn't it?
You're building a Sea Parks
out of mashed potato!
There are 12 exits, Moss.
12 exits for only 200 people.
You going Close Encounters crazy, Roy.
You need to let it go.
To have killed anyone, the fire
has to start here, here and here.
And close in like this.
But how's it spreading?
There's no wood in a Sea Parks arena.
And why is there no wood?
Because it rots.
And why does it rot?
Because of all the water.
Damn, that mash looks tasty!
Password?
You didn't ask for a password before.
Moss!
Where's Moss?
It's payday.
He's probably gone to Namco.
Where's Namco?
Flip! It's an iPhone!
It's a flipping iPhone
in the crane machine!
Oh! Plum out of coin!
Moss!
Oh, Moss.
What am I going to do?
What are you...
How did you get in there?
Through the hole.
Why?
There's an iPhone, Jen.
An actual iPhone.
I need your password.
I need the password
of the translation programme.
Help me get the iPhone first.
I can't move my arms.
- No.
- I need to get it through the shoot.
Someone else will take it if you don't.
I'm sure they're not giving it away.
The engineer must have dropped it.
No, no, no. It's a prize, it's a prize,
you've got to help.
- I don't have time.
- But it's an iPhone, Jen.
I may be able to get an iPhone
without giving any money to Apple.
I'll be living the dream.
What's the password?
Moss! Moss!
"Oh, I'm so excited
about the sea lion show.
"Oh, yay!"
"Um, ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Luigi,
"Joe and Slippery Pete!"
"Yay, yay! Whoo! Whoo!"
"Oh, no! What's all this smoke?"
Oh, smoke.
Where will I get smoke?
Yes.
I got it! I got it! I got it!
Where is it?
I think I must be blocking it.
I'll try and move to clear the passage.
Come on, Moss.
Come on, Moss, you can do it. Push.
Come on, Moss. Keep breathing.
- Push!
- Shut up!
- You can do it, Moss.
- I hate you!
- Why are you saying that?
- I don't know. Stop talking!
Come on, Moss. Come on!
Perfect.
It's coming! I can see it,
I can see the start button.
One last push! One, two, three, push!
Come on, Moss. Push! Push!
It's beautiful.
Password!
Where the hell have you been?
Sorry. It was just...
It doesn't matter. So far,
he's satisfied with general laughter.
Mr Bernatelli, meet Jen.
Viennetta, Fiat Punto.
Leave that laptop outside.
- No. What?
- We have to think about security, Jen.
How do we know that laptop isn't somehow
able to connect to the internet?
- No, no, it is a...
- Then get it out of here!
Look! Look at this. Look at how long
it's taking to go on fire.
And this is made of matches.
So, first of all, I'd like to extend
the warmest welcome to Mr Bernatelli
and hope today is the beginning of
a long and fruitful partnership.
Alora.
Il forior extenderay a warma welcome
a Mr Bernatelli.
E macarena, macchiato, Luca Brasi,
Gianluca Viallis, Sophia Loren.
He says it's a pleasure to be here.
Hey.
I see. So, if the fire started here,
and they were there,
then there's no way
they could've escaped.
So they must've been there.
Ah! Ah!
Oh, look at this. Actually... Stop it!
Go out.
Ow, my hands!
Passe con Baccarat con du Super Mario.
I have always wanted to visit England.
Hey.
Uh, I'm looking forward to sampling some
of your famous English food.
Well, I'm sure that can be arranged.
Um, bella, bella, arrangella.
So, what do you want to talk about?
Ah, now you listen to me, Bernatelli.
Me listena Bernatelli.
I hope by the end of this meeting,
we can become firm friends.
...firma frienda.
I like you and I like what you've done
with your company.
...compania.
Hopefully, we can join forces and plough
our way through these uncertain times.
Hopefully join-a force-a
di plough uncertain time-a.
What do you say?
Bernatelli and Reynholm Industries.
Together we'll be bigger than ever.
Bernatelli e Reynholm Industries,
della fella bella, bigger than evera.
Hey! I'm going to stand up
and start talking slightly louder.
Do you like my suit or not?
The woman to my left
smells like she's been for a run.
This meeting is going better
than you might think.
I love what you have done
with this office.
Can I borrow some of your erotic art?
For how long?
On second thoughts, I'm going to go.
Never contact me again,
because I'm mental.
Well, that was a waste of time.
Next time you have a bright idea, Linda,
keep it to yourself.
- But...
- And for God's sake, get a shower!
- Oh, my God! Roy!
- Hiya.
Oh, my God, you poor thing.
Look at your hands.
How did that happen?
It's kind of hard to explain.
- But what...
- I don't want to talk about it!
Moss!
Hello?
Hello!
Starting to get pretty lonely now.
These toys may smell of wee
come the morn.